A-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a-a
Unseen game reveals its name
He was like smiling and he check you
Thank you big screen everybody, why did you forget to do that because he was cammed up he was cammed up
What's happening?
His name was Aiden something, and it looked like a Bradley
a little bit, and then I was like, he wasn't shy.
Aiden is Tony.
No, oh my god.
So what would you rate it?
Negative.
I was not impressed.
There was so much going on.
Not impressed?
I've never seen a black wanker before.
I just saw the smile on his face.
I can't say it's all I can see was a beard.
And I'm a kid, he's a fan.
I saw something. I saw somebody peeing. I was like, what the hell is that?
And he was happy to do it. He wasn't happy.
He was. He was happy to pick and shit. Pissing on all over the place. I hope he had a buck.
We're gonna have nightmares.
Yeah, I never seen the blank.
I was in the middle of answering a serious question.
May I finish? May I finish answering the question?
Sure. May I finish? So, Seth, you were talking about a date.
I've never had gay friend then so this is where Mr. Psyche becomes an ambassador.
Psyche.
uh based on the kindness that he's shared with me i feel a responsibility for his kindness
with people who are like i mean i don't want to say like him but people you know who who are
part of that community i think what i was saying got convoluted bro like you're you're totally
If Sykes your first gay friend getting to know him would probably open you up to you know being like oh, you know
I was hoping you're saying what I meant is more like
What's like for example, what's your racial background?
That's Alexander McQueen, yeah, so if some white guy was met you and right away was like, oh, you're Hispanic
Oh, I have lots of Hispanic friends like I love Hispanic people. Oh that you'd be like, okay
That's all I meant. Yeah, I see what you mean exactly. And they'll be so pretentious and fake
That I'd rather have somebody call me a fucking spick
That's what I do. I don't know if anybody has family. I'm like, hey, what's up? What's going on?
You do that all the time. I would call her sand people from
Oh
It's not
You got the nerve to say that with a Confederate flag behind you
That is not it's a battle flag
We beat you
I need you to full screen 30 diamonds like Wiggins full screen 30 diamonds. She's gonna torque. No
Uh, nobody want to see that fucking steenus
You go for that because
Yeah, I did
Oh, we got a we got a full house. Okay. Okay. Thank you got a full house
171 people
So someone just
I think it's interesting to even comment on it, just because, is that my mic one sec?
It is Nick's, I got it, Nick's.
She's clearly up here in a very diverse group of people and she has nothing hateful to say
to anybody.
assimilated or like related to someone that you might think it is and I think
that people need to get over some symbolism maybe not all of it but I
agree I don't want to burst your bubble but you are being bodied right now I
hope you know that it's okay it's okay what's bought it
when somebody has a hundred real viewers somebody said somebody bought somebody
bought yeah that's time elder welcome to primetime podcasting buddy
I admire Joker weren't you over and Tommy chat talking shit about
I was laughing yeah I was laughing at Tommy talk shit at
like that's what a friend does that's what a friend does right homies jealous
that we have more viewers
I don't think, I don't think you are a part of we, you know what I'm saying, psych, psych, you know what I'm saying, it's psych.
You pretend to help psych, but you don't help do shit.
come on i don't know like 15 uh what do you call it i married one yankee and that was a
fucking mistake i don't want to be honest i'm blunt but um
Honest no, but dude. I wasn't talking shit on psych on Tommy James podcast
I was mainly just laughing at Tommy James
He said that you're too sensitive you're too gay and all this stuff
Podcasters you don't belong in the community and he's saying Tommy James is saying that you're tweaked out and all this crazy nonsense
Tommy has a lot to say when he wasn't like so clean himself
He's come up with a whole narrative against you like 20 different narratives to take you
Oh, Tommy, we love our psyche.
I caught pieces of it Nancy. I did but I definitely heard Joker. It wasn't if
Psych would have seen it. He wouldn't have been happy. I know that for a fact
So it's my job as a you know a friend this site to let him know that Joker you a fake-ass
No, dude, I can't laugh about someone why didn't you stand up for so I can go this isn't appropriate
I tried I failed I was three on one by all do one case
Yeah, I got ganked up on, I lost.
It's okay, I didn't see it, I didn't see it, and it's like, you know, it's a mess too.
I heard you, that's right, it's like, I have a bunch of people fucking with me.
But you should have cussed them out.
I tried to literally stand up for myself, but it just made it worse, so.
Yeah, well, I understand how that can be on panel and all these man at me because I like said oh
Seven five bucks and you can come back on the panel and stuff like that and he just like
Here porn bomber, you know, that's all he does
Yeah, I understand this about drama
If you don't care what people say about you, then you will continue to be the genuine you.
Because somebody will always say something about you and then these people will continue
to bring drama to your doorstep and tell you what somebody else said about you and it still
doesn't matter.
And you know it's better to have it rather have people talking about me than not talking about
Yeah
Ultimately they're promoting my show they're like it's getting interest up and people are gonna say oh
so I got gang banged on I got gang banged on when I tried to stand up for each
side so you have to you have to literally at least like give me an A for
effort okay thank you
give you a fucking A for effort no dude these are called he cursed me out and
told me that I'm a I beat up old people and that I'm a fucking terrible person
that I should just leave the earth and all this nonsense because I'm friends
with psychoicants
Yeah, well, you know, it's like it's okay. It's like, you know, I miss it
I would have liked to go watch it because I like the other the other day
Someone had like psyches though a weirdo lurker and they talked about me for like half hour
They're like, oh, okay. Look at this pampered. Look at this pampered ass
24 hours and on his daybed
I'm on my daybed. Hey, this is my daybed
I think Tommy overreacted, and I think that's serious, you know what I'm saying?
Like, besides the part where you just be hitting on men and shit, and they're not gay, other than that, I mean, you're cool, you know what I'm saying?
I don't even know if I hit on Tommy.
Okay, tell me who isn't, tell me it's not my type.
I don't think so.
I don't think Tommy put me inside, no.
Uh psyche when bronze bird comes in here. I have to tell you the weirdest dream
I had last night about you and him. Okay. What? Yeah, it was a gay dream
Definitely was oh my god
I will save that. It was it was the weirdest dream ever like ever ever
Yeah, he got into a sleeping bag and then he went to sleep on the floor and then he fixed his head out
It was this black guy, and I was like you're gay, and he's like oh sometimes shut up or something
I can't wait to tell like, you know, like everybody
I made friends with psycho wakens. I used to be way more homophobic when I let that make friends
I used to be just he's he's made me
It's never hated gay people. I just like to call people, you know the the f a double
Oh, bags? Yeah.
I'd like to do that, but like, that's just what I like to say, but like, you know, but I've noticed that, you know, like, maybe my opinions of what I thought gay people were aren't as stereotypical as I thought.
Thank you. Reminds me of myself.
Your doctor?
He's a great ambassador for the actual gay community and he's not an SJW, he's not a weird or anything like that.
He's just like a normal dude that you can talk to and identify with.
And you can ask him questions about it and he doesn't get offended.
Yeah
The only gay guy I would actually like want to make love to
Have a lot of gay friends and they're like very like feminine, but psyche's got a masculinity about him, you know
He dies
And turn him straight, you know, oh, I will live in a big enough city that has a gay district
where you can like go to a street and it's all gay restaurants and bars and
shops. Is that a thing where any of you live? We do too.
Yeah, it's called the game on the game on the cake.
Is that Alex Alex?
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
Alex a cop.
He a Brooklyn cop.
New York.
I see it. I see it. Okay. Yeah. He's a New York cop. Let me see it. Okay. Psych with
psych. Psych pride would like for you to put that on them. You know what I'm saying?
Another handcuff. What? Yeah. Yeah. He had to put two of them together because he couldn't
get the one of the range. Oh, God, please don't handcuff yourself. Like, enough. Get
out. Oh, he can get out. He's got the keys. Where that motherfucking Canada draw yet, man?
What do you mean like where am I at in the world or just like right now you change your
name untrackable.
Show me the statue on Saskia oh yeah you why did you why did you bad why did you time
out somebody because they said I love you page I don't think I did for your case so
you're not you're not Canada dry and chat.
So you don't remember doing that
Eldo sometimes when you time people out for some reason they said something else and it's like when they delete all the comments
And so maybe it was for some other comment. They may come off side come on. That was the only time out. He did
Because there was a person talking shit last night me and Alex were like going back and forth with a couple people
Yo, you and at what primarily Alex was being in people for saying regular shit
It's like cool with it fuck it, you know what I'm saying, but when you go to sleep they definitely ban people for no fucking reason
I'll check I'll take every day. I'll take a band. You can't you can't check the band. It ain't the banalists. They're smart
They time them out
It's elbow big elbow
That's probably why we have so many viewers there people aren't popping up in the chats because you have a rogue mods
They're just time people are
Does that shit almost every night
Have you looked at your um block list?
I mean, look right. I'll take right now. I'll take right now. Okay. You'll definitely realize it eventually, you know
I had like 122 people and then there was only like, I don't know
Definitely
I just figured out, you know me
I guess I guess that y'all don't got power in real life. So y'all got a time people out
We dealt with kids like you in school, you know, yeah, yeah, there's no there's nobody on the block list. Okay, so that's good. Yeah, I
Think we're all right here
Pretty much
I'm just making a little piece bread here with garlic. Oh, that's done so good
And they don't do it that that's how you know, it's being done maliciously, you know
They wait till you go to sleep to do it. They don't do it. Why are you up?
Yeah, that's right. I'll go
Every time he passes out and that's why I told him he's got to stop the streams when he goes to sleep and can't leave
I'm running like that. Good
You know people can't be trusted
So that's why I have a moment of silence, so awkward silence, so awkward silence.
The only time I've ever blocked or deleted someone's chat is if they're disrespecting or like saying they're gonna come.
No, I mean, I got the proof where you did it, you know what I'm saying? I have to have just screen shot it.
I got the one where you hit somebody for saying I love you Paige, you know?
So I definitely got that if you're a candidate.
Why would I mute that?
Unless it was a regardo in which case I was just muting a bunch of shit. He said or swami either regard
Yeah, it was swami. I think it was swami. So do you have a do you have do you dislike swami?
Swami, yeah
So do you think maybe you got a little personal vendetta against Swami where you're you're just
Like fuck you um, I don't really like swammy. So I'm kind of a troll
You know, so so psych psych if you're good with me going after people I dislike cuz I dislike a lot of motherfuckers, you know
You know, let me let me start hitting people when you go to sleep
It started more when they were threatening to come to my house and talking weird shit
Yeah, but that don't mean go ahead and take over another person's panel and start timing them out because you know
I mean like that's not cool. This ain't your house. You'll visit it. I'm just saying man. Yeah, man
Well, thanks for being here to set things set the record straight. You know what I'm saying, man
We need more people like you out here
Let's all let's all just
I'm just chopping some garlic
Bag of chips, what are you doing? Oh, shut up
Okay
Oh, shit. I'm sitting down already. Okay, we're good.
When you put your finger, I added some I had someone I had someone.
Yo, so I'm live streaming right now, psych. I'm live streaming everybody in my
chat, go to psych awaken, stream and give him a like and everybody from psych
awaken shot, go to my stream, give me a like and we'll vice versa back and forth
for growing the communities, taking over the panel, all the fucking losers
and we're going to fucking win the war.
blackout Andy you were poor and you fucking eat smore it is six people come over here
he actually like exists like imagine being like i i think that is crazy blackout Andy exists
it's like a germ that's just fucking living it's crazy it is he threatens people that come to the
show like what are you drinking flirty it's kind of gross it's the basic purple punch this one's gross
We can't one of them little ones. You know, they're saying Joker. Where are these people I was gonna buy one of them
So basically this community is a is a mixture of all of the panellas into one channel
Tracy does not kill your ass. It's like I'm pretty fucking drunk like this my second one and like I'm already halfway done
They tastey
The strawberry one is tasty, but the purple one is disgusting. Okay, so get the strawberry one
That's the best one. Yeah, cuz I mean, I love strawberries. So I am biased. Yeah, I like strawberry, too
Yeah, isn't there a shit ton of flavors? Yeah, there's like a there's a couple cuz
We don't have them in Canada.
They just came out in Massachusetts about two months ago and I went to pick one up and
my liquor store lady went, uh-uh, Tray.
So I went back and got a fucking bottle of vodka
This one's not for you. Oh, you know what she made me buy she did little vodka one and it was dill pickle
Little dill pickle shooter. She says that is so tasty. So I've got one in the frieza
Drink on vibes. It's um, it's the other version of a beatbox and the vibes are so much more stronger than
Everybody
I like to drink and get drunk, but I don't like taste alcohol if that makes sense. So
The more flavor, the easier.
Tequila's the best for that.
Sometimes I hate the piece of alcohol, but like when I'm like.
I drunk myself straight on tequila one time.
I fed the tequila and I drank it all and I tell you what, boy.
Ever since I've just smelled that shit, make me sick.
Yeah, for some reason I can drink tequila the smoothest.
Yeah, oh wow.
There's 260 in the room.
I used to be able to.
Pretty cool.
268 in the room. Yes, chat. We all need to we all need to know that we have to come together when it comes to blackout
Andy we have to not let
He's he's probably the one that porn bomb stream
This was a real guy white winkle
You can download it you can download a program Tracy and you can play the video on the screen. It looks like oh really
Well, nowadays you can do any of that stuff. There's a lot of programs on the computer
Programs is of the video
I posted on my Instagram already, so I had my snapchat, so I really don't
No dude, I'm not going to post your content, believe it or not, I'm not going to post your
only fans content.
I'm talking about the video I just sent you, I already posted that one on Facebook, I mean
Instagram.
Can I label it Flirty Diamond Torx for Joker TV?
Sure.
Publicity sales.
I can help you before you diamond, I can help you with your management.
No, I just, you know, I already have someone I make content with, but if you ever in California, we can.
You're looking for joints right here.
I don't think this poor guy needs to be.
Actually, never mind. I got to argument with this person just now.
Oh, those are comfy.
I got someone.
Wow.
I'm excited to put them on, yeah.
Those are sharks. They are I like them
Hey, Jamie Rose, what's up, Jamie Rose?
Check out these ones. Hi, Jamie
It's a joker only bottle. I only top all those
I
Big big fan, who are you?
People tolerate this homosexual who's like a fucking
Hey acts what kind of motorbike do you have a Harley?
I had a Harley and then I traded it for Mercedes Benz.
Oh, okay.
Something more like road safe, kind of like road.
No, and then I went and bought,
it looks like a dresser, it's a jack piece of shit.
Oh.
What is it?
It's a shaft driven bike,
but it's on a fat bob frame and it's just a beater.
It's, let me see.
Fuck it's a jet piece of shit. What do you call it? It's a motorcycle
My cousins are scoring a police special and a survey car Harley. Oh
Now I have a
1964 to con a wine band that used to belong to the town for the fire department
I ain't gonna lie to you Tracy
You look like you was fine back in the day when he was about 30 40. I mean you got a picture
Oh, I do.
No, no, no.
Come on, Tracy.
Let me see your picture, because I'm telling you, man.
You fine, man.
You know what she has done.
Well, Lady O'Han.
I don't know.
I have any.
All of them are nudes.
I might get the show off.
Tracy, you need that band?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm trying to find one.
Hit my DM.
Come on.
Hit my DM for that one.
I try and find one that's not a nude.
Let me see. I got to go into the safe. What's up thing chat? Look at Tracy man. Tracy power was a badass
Tracy's no bad. No, no, I'm saying yeah, but I'm saying 30 40
Yeah, cuz I'm 59 now. I'll be 60 in September
I'm just saying.
Hey, what's up?
Corruption is real.
Hey, Bernie.
Listen, listen, I'm put a record for the record. Oh, you put a week. I've never seen
So I'm legal I'm legal
You can't wait by no green. No, they don't got green cars man. That's it. That's the United States territory US territory
Oh, you born here. Yeah. Yeah
I'm American
no there's one little set is this going to be a photo of you sitting on your hog tracy
um no i don't have a picture of the motorcycle all right you got a lot uh full screen
okay once again this is my best friend
I don't want to see your best friend. No, this is me with my best friend
I got the confederate put on oh that's the American flag I stole that flag hold on I'll find in it
There's no nipples showing okay, there's no nipples showing
But that's me
No nipples
Told you I knew it I knew it
This is this is me and let me see if there's any breast. Oh, there's a nipple someone. You can't
Put my finger over it. Don't even risk it. Don't even risk it down.
Oh my god, that was with Papa Phil.
Oh, you have some fun.
Papa Phil, a lucky mother fucker.
Yeah, two y'all.
Yeah, that was, and let me see.
He's got legs.
You can't see that one.
You lived a good life.
What's up there, Chad?
She lived a good life, didn't she?
She's still living a good life.
I'll see that.
Y'all see that?
Come on. Oh my god. There you go. So that's part of a club. Yes. Yeah. Right. I know.
Um, okay. This one is part of the cut to the biker cut. Titty out. Oh, wow. Look at your body,
Tracy. That's crazy.
Let me see that one. You can't oh shit. That's me
No, no, oh, there's me naked in front of the 10 can't see that one
These were in the
Yo, what's what's gonna happen when you pass away and your grandkids go through your shit
You got all them great kids my son's a queer
He's gay like site. Oh, yeah, really like real gay gay
Damn that's why I see get along with you so much say she had a gay fucking
Me when I'm dressed, but I'm smoking a joint
Wait, I can't see it. I I'm looking up. Let me see
I want to see Tracy. No, I want to see Tracy. I'm sorry, sir
We don't want to see that you're like here. Yeah
That's me with I connect me to a little one-on-one session
Yeah
We're these at the clubhouse Tracy. I guess cool. These are all done at the clubhouse
These are the vigilantes
Wow, Tracy wait, what would I do? What's with me? Do my homework mermaid mermaids? Are you on my dick?
It's all vigilante clubhouse bitches. I was
22 something like that
Yeah, and I always was naked cuz I hate clothes
That's awesome. Yeah, that's it the front one and that that's me in the front
I'm with this shirt on sit on the stool
Cool
Let's make this stuff your style to it. Oh, I you know absolutely, you know it
By then I got shit. I was in jail for the first time with seven years old
Well, I appreciate you showing them pictures, Tracy.
Yeah, Tracy, you're a cutie pie.
Were you able to date with somebody who was blood?
Women can't be patrolled just but yes, I was part of the club.
So you were an old lady.
Yeah, no, I'm 59 years old, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
Somebody asked me who was my top three and I said my girl big tizzle
Tracy was number two and vegan was number three. I said this about two months ago
He looks about three months pregnant now.
Y'all ever see vegan on a stripper pole?
Keep playing with your bulls.
Oh, I bet she's good.
Listen, listen.
I bet vegan is fucking fine on a pole.
Listen, y'all, this is my vegan right here.
This is my vegan right here.
This is vegan, baby.
You know what I'm saying?
No, Elda, thank you.
This is vegan.
This is vegan right here.
You have it the same.
And vegan ain't got no dick, like fucking Tranny Diamond.
I'm just saying, don't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's shut the fuck up.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
She did that with stroke off, she peed on his beard.
Ew.
Listen, Trani Diamond, you, you already-
I believe that Mike would love to be donezo.
I told you, when I said you was donezo, I meant it.
When I said you was donezo, I meant it.
It's literally-
It's not doing it right for you.
It's over.
It's obviously not doing it right for you.
I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just saying, I'm just
Crystal or even
Y'all ever see that show, what is it that's so cold on Netflix the biker show
Yeah, yeah, some of the anarchy. Oh, yeah, you have something like that going on. I know
Y'all was running guns, huh? Okay, I got I got a felony in
Virginia for breaking the 9-11 law for guns
Damn, I was one of the first ones that law had just come out and they got me for guns
Bastard, I just got in the fucking Virginia too. I wasn't even there two months and I was already a felon
Bastard
That's okay. I still got guns
I still got my shit. We popping shit in this motherfucker
I still got my guns, baby. I got my police gun there, I got my gun.
You're safe inside your nudes as your gun.
Oh no, I've got a 32 snub known as this.
No, Tracee, to save you this, let's segue away from your...
I've got a segue.
Yeah, let's talk about your segue, and would you ride that?
Crystal and Chad, come up here, Crystal.
No, I broke its head on it, so I gave it to you.
Run it, run it, run it!
What the fuck is he saying that shit?
He's saying that.
I'm on rogue chill out dog. You're saying Mexico instead. I've got I've got a
That's a mountain bike that does about is this set by 40 miles an hour. No
Joker
No, it's you rogue. I could tell bro. I got a six
No, you're told your tone change man to align
Yeah
Just a bugger.
Guessing the full moon tonight
Full moon and these holes ain't acting right
You need to fix your shit, man, you got all them costumes by a fucking
head set I think he's a male entertainer
Where we going site you're going to the whole boots and then now
We're gonna hold food and then to the taco truck
He never talks so why the fuck is your mic on I don't think I don't think I've ever heard his voice
There's not any of you here you're all silent. What's going on here?
You guys are staring at me. We're waiting on we're waiting on crystal marita join. We need crystal up here
I think they smoke some widows
So I want to say this that what we're gonna do is we're gonna take over the panel first
We're taking over the panel first. I need like the whole box of all the gummies beat us beat us up
If you run the panel first beat a failed now it's psych's panel first. He owns what?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I
Claimed everything else
Oh, by the way, Joker, thank you, I posted it on my thing
Mexican
It's be this kitty game joke or Mexican. It's really really sweet
You know site like
He likes.
He likes everything.
He's like like Mexican.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
somebody told you they fucking uh
Gramps was fucking paying over it's like, well fuck it, it's my fuck it, don't be a rat
he don't even contribute
that looks amazing
I know I love those salads
yeah, that looks fucking amazing
oh I do, I love those salads
it's so good
I love that
get a little juice there and the juice off
Can you just ask somebody where like, you know, where the something I was no, what you do is get a shopping cart and you accidentally
bought somebody and then start a conversation and that's how you pick up a piece.
Tracy's a pro.
That video footage is horrible, man.
You need a new camera if you're going to be a streamer.
Oh, look at that.
Nice salmon there. You need you need a you need a new you need to off on 16
Look at that potato
Can you calm down
I'm just passing by you ain't gonna be here tomorrow. You feel me more than likely you ain't gonna be here tomorrow
And you shall cast judgment upon me for it am I right?
You don't only motherfucker, I know that that pretends to be a retard
Just go next to somebody else and we'll all just go mean
Oh my god, he just looked over for a guy.
Bam.
Meow.
It's like we're being taken out right now with him.
No.
The Eldos don't mean that.
That's Eldos.
The Eldos the one, the mean kid in the buzz
is just talking shit and I'm stuck.
It's like, ooh, I'm too fucking good for this.
I'm too good for this road trip.
Don't show your credit card.
I was like, oh, yeah, my parents are too rich for this shit.
I don't need to be here.
This is a stick up.
Put your hands up, motherfucker.
Looks like I have phones on.
I'm sorry, dude.
Can I have all your money?
No, Zach.
He's got his headset on.
Nobody can hear him.
Oh, god, good.
He's got his hands in.
And as we're out on the outing end, we're going to shut the fuck up.
How's that shut the fuck up?
Let's rewind this.
Is this live? You can't rewind it to the game. You see that dance to the video.
What the fuck are you doing?
Can't we fucking take you anywhere else?
Oh, so many backpacks.
Almost exactly a year ago, on a Sunday.
He's running away, dude. He's like, yeah, he's got his beer and he's gone
The both ways before you cross the street boom no
No boom
Oh
Boom we
And 232 and chat it's like popular boy. I'm telling you man. I think this Tommy beef. God. God, you know people coming through
That's cuz Joker here man Joker bringing these 232 man
He helping sight
We're making the five hundred five hundred
I'm not a magician, dude. Yeah, I think you are
Jonathan Panto has his rug them it is cringe. Well, he has a black eye
like he ate too much food and somehow we have to fucking pay for his treatment
Oh, there's tree frog another person that comes over. Oh my god. I know a bunch of people in the chat
Jonathan Pantola. I hope you fucking die
They're here for you Tracy
No, but I know a bunch of them cuz they come over when I
Roll one up, okay, nobody
I don't know, nobody do give me a sample
Okay, uh fish or your fish to fish
Chicken this is tacos
two beef two chicken
Your thank you
Yes, you have. I know. You should tell him that you have 230 people watching and if you could advertise his truck thingy.
And tell him to subscribe and like your channel. Yeah, this tree frog. We love tree frog.
What's that man?
Nampai Rosto.
Okay, orange sauce is very spicy.
Red sauce is hot, sir.
So you need to make sure he let YouTube know
that he getting mad at that way
they don't fuck with his channel.
It would love it because there'd be advertisements for them.
Can you get the video out on the side site?
No.
If I had a business, I would want to be promoted on a channel where 230 people are watching me.
Um, no, but YouTube being...
No, because it's fake.
Because it's fake people.
It ain't real people.
What are you talking about?
They're not fake people.
You said fake people.
Beta, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm eating an apple. What are you talking about? So you're telling me that you really think that it's really 232 people watching right now
I'm saying that's what they're gonna see and they're gonna be like, okay, there may be like here's a free talk
I like that green do you know YouTube policy if they find out cuz they might think it's him doing it they terminate channels
Well, you know in a Lisa's chat in a Lisa's chat every day there's 500 people
There's like 30 people in chat so if they do it every day in a Lisa's and she's monetized
Yeah, but how do you know she bought it?
You're the only one saying bought it over and over and over again like you're trying to get
Don't cross out your bitch ass. Oh, you don't want over there with the enemy talking shit about
105 I can talk to Tommy James in the house
I'm the one that got fucking roasted.
No, no, I doubt that.
That's right. Press one if it's not a bot,
and it's about the only way to tell.
And then you're the type of nigga to say slick-ass shit, like,
man, fuck the motherfucker that don't turn their camera on.
But as soon as you're on this panel with my fucker
that don't turn their camera on, you don't say a fucking thing,
you pussy.
I already know who Bita is, dude.
I don't care about who Bita is.
I've already seen her face. I don't ever seen her face.
Yeah, so why don't you say it?
The fuck you you wait till you over there with the motherfucking IP to haters to say oh fuck
I can't be that boring if I was able to get a thousand subscribers on my channel and I didn't have to turn my fucking camera on
Drama is it
You think they really continue to want to watch white boys get drunk and
That's why my fucking ip2 is dead right now. Yeah, cuz there's nobody with watching
Well, yeah, if you're up here in New England, it's fucking we're walking to seven inches inches of snow this morning
Yeah, I can't do that fence riding shit, man. I'm gonna call that shit. How I see I don't give a fuck who get
Dude, I have to be nice to Tommy James. That's to be nice to IP to has to be nice like away
I mean, I fuck with it. I fuck with him. Yeah, but like he was pressing you like you know me and then you tried to like
They think they think that I'm helping psycho a kids get viewers, so they're mad that I'm not helping
But I'm not even doing anything. I think it's blackout Angie trolling me the whole time
But a day you say last night when sake will sleep that you're over here to help him get his channel popular or whatever
I was over here to come on camera and make the stream more entertaining not to make him like
I'm here to be more
The moon is a marvelous sight
So tell us a story about you sask. What are you doing right now?
Oh, I'm just eating a good zone here on Instagram.
Instagram, I don't have one of those things.
I got one of those and all I got was a fucking girl.
Trying to fuck with me.
So I'm gonna ask this to chat.
Chat, can body get you demonetized?
Cause everybody that's been monetized knows this shit.
You know, I'm monetized.
Well, the thing is, dude, is that people don't buy other people's things.
Anybody can send anybody to people's channels.
I'm monetized.
I've been in your team, you know.
You be not no disrespect, but you're better.
You know, because somebody else can do it.
I got it, baby.
I got to do what, Elzo?
I said, you only be having like 10 or 12 people over there.
You're not getting bodies.
No, but Eldo, somebody else can bought for you, so you don't even have to sell it.
Yeah, that's the problem. That is true, but I'm saying that if you look it up.
Nobody is bought here. They're all real people. They all love psyche.
Do you know I had a whole bunch of real people came in and I got $50 at night.
A bunch of people, I don't know, came in and started throwing money at me by the end of
the night at $50.
Hey, you guys, TTS on all the blogs and everybody, TTS on money.
Don't talk about it. Don't mean you two gonna fucking y'all thinking that you two gonna do something because we talking about it
I've been down there naked with paper tape on my titty nipples and I can have fun and I'm on it
monetize
I put on short shorts and tape on my nipples, so you can't see my titty nipples, but I said they're for six months.
I'm not going to call them your titty nipples.
Hello.
As they are.
They're the barber's price and effect.
You have titty, and then you have nipple.
No, it's great.
Yeah, and one nipples pierced
No, no, no, no, no, you don't
Oh God girl. Oh God girl
Pain pain. I was on the motorcycle, right?
Listen, I'm telling you I was on my motorcycle on the highway
And I was following the band of guys going to a party and we had to pull over the rest off and I grabbed one of them and
Made them suck on that damn titty nipple that had to ring in it
to get that motherfucker warm so i could do the next 40 miles to the party um no i've
had my nipples pierced before so i'm gonna get some repairs it's never hurt me but
but then i'll tell you what you ain't got no damn brain
i've had my blood tattoo yeah i haven't seen tracy in chat in a minute the other tracy what the
she's been working hard yeah she's works a lot we love you Tracy and then
Paige I like Tracy too this sweetheart yeah I never met an asshole Tracy in my
life
No, I'm a Virgo. It's had to piss me off.
Is that the real blackout and chires out of fake blackout? That might be the real blackout.
My brother is the Virgo and the only word that will piss him off is asshole, if I call him an asshole.
But see I've been called every name in the books
No, I can call him anything though. He won't get mad, but it's just asshole or I don't know
He gets mad at that you get really mad
Well, there's something you did as a kid. It's because he has an asshole sometimes
Well, you're spoiled brat. Yeah, he's he'd know he farted on me all the time when I was a kid you stick your
He would torture me and throw spiders on me
Oh
Yeah, that's the real black he reached dream or some or no he's is he streaming or streaming
He's watching while he's streaming maybe
Late enough for him to be on somebody told him joker was talking about and that's what happened
He's been in the chat the whole time dude
He watches it every time I come up here. He loves me. I'm his favorite streamer. Oh
Really
Yeah blackout Annie sadly he was born with autism so he can't he doesn't can't comprehend that I
Love him, but he can't comprehend
Well, he's another small brat
Yeah, yes
Right back
You got love these rich kids. Yeah, they're spoiled brats of blackout and you know you guys are really quiet for a nine-person podcast
What's going on here? Dude? What's going on? I'm reading it. Yeah
I'm fine on phone right now. So I'm looking at a psyche
Broke my iPod, so I'm buying a new a new thing right now fucking broke it
I broke my damn charger the other day, brand new 12 foot cord and the son of a bitch fell off the waterbed.
I hate chargers from the gas station. I fucking don't fuck with them no more because I bought a new charge from the gas station and it gave out.
But thankfully I found my original Apple charger so like I'm done now, but that shit was so annoying.
It stopped working and I just fucking bought it.
Yeah, that still runs out in like a month.
Yeah, I never got passed around, baby.
Never got passed around. I wasn't one of those broads. I was always with a sergeant in arms
Now I worked with said the sergeant in arms. I was his dog
Dogs don't have to fuck other men only bitches do and I was a dog
So the answer to question is no read your rulebook
You're okay. Thank you. That's what they are. They're just okay. I am kind of I do you know, I know Lisa does you know her
She's bought it like every every night like 500 people like I don't know about anything. You don't know what's going on
You just know you really don't like you just guessing. Yeah, just have fun
And I would people are saying everyone
You guys everybody like and like you know
Donate do tts do membership. I'll be able to get those numbers myself
I'll be able to get those numbers like I was good
I got like a hundred people in the chat through their day, and I'm happy with that. It's like I don't need like
Maybe you are getting people maybe you're before a lurking and you know
Restreaming and watching you
It's better to be honest with them because you know, I'm saying like it's obvious, bro. Like what the fuck?
Yeah, there's nothing you can do about it. He leaves the Jordanus streams with obvious bots every day
Nobody does anything. No, I honestly I did honestly think because she's a known figure
She used to work with Howard Stern. So I figured she at least had four, you know
In her chat be moving fast as hell too, you know, I'm saying this chat moves, but
We're having a conversation
No, thanks. You're not a Bob, but you say, you know, you say
It's like
Oh, Dennis weeds good. Oh
You're known to box the Joker because that's what Amber saying Amber go way back. So have you bought it before?
I bet he has to be honest. I'm gonna hear not to get a 50 question by you. No, I haven't dude
Right, let me tell you this all your favorite big streamers like Aiden Ross and I show speed they use bots
Yeah, yeah
And it's like and if they're so and it's like if they and it's like
They can't they have no control over who does that right and so it's like don't yeah, and they so it's like how can you?
You can and so look what it is though is that psycho wakens has got two case-ups now
And I'm helping him with the streams by joining getting people to join and helping make content
You sound you sound like fucking Empress you act like you're doing something for them and really not doing shit
It's happening naturally
Let me tell you something dude
Anybody can buy anyone's channel so people will purposely do it the people they hate to try to get them in trouble
So obviously someone that hates him is doing it. That's what I'm saying. Y'all want to keep it quiet a secret
Instead of letting Scythe know, that's what I'm doing.
I don't know any secrets.
Like if I knew, I would be like, this is what's going on.
I don't know what's going on.
Just roll with it and don't let them win.
You just admitted that people get in trouble for it.
No, no streamers will try to do anything to try to ruin anyone's dream
It's not better to know the streamer know that owns his platform or it's better to just stay quiet about it
I
See ya
Also Lisa's monetized but um she doesn't um
She doesn't have a membership and she doesn't really get many super chats because she has the he's a power chat set up
You know and so I mean so they're active
Dude, I'm just saying dude some people like literally will watch a stream and not type because they don't want to be trolled
So you know that we're working
I've always I've always had like like probably 20 people that don't say anything
I've had I've had like last night I had like 30 people in the chat and only one person was talking and stuff like that
So now you're lurking. Yeah
I could be busy cooking or something have you in the background and I put you
You up against my way, but now watch you guys. Well, I fucking cook
You know, because it's loud, you know, I'm doing dishes and shit, so I can't get on panel, but I can at least
Show that there's one more in your chat. You know, I mean by watching
And the view I read I have read every single YouTube rule and all the shit dude, so I know that he's I can't do it
Okay dude, if you end your stream and restart it over and over again, it's just going to
destroy your channel.
So just keep streaming psych and nothing will happen to you because you are a victim.
You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, I've done 12 day streams and it was the music that finally because I was like five hours from 12 days on a live stream
Wow, and the motherfucker got me from music
I had five hours and 17 minutes and some fucking weird shit for 12 hour Mac and
our 12-day mark and the son of a bitch who's got my stream
I was so fucking pissed I was going for the world record and if I made it or the record Guinness
Book of World Records right and the thing is if I'd made it to 12 hours and over I had already
beaten somebody else for doing a fucking live stream that means you got to see me eat you got
For 12 days it started I was sick and I was bored and nobody talked to because I live by myself
So I was on the water bed, and I'm like
No, fuck I started streaming and I don't talk was look good
Is that a taco?
I got poor tacos
It's for
They put a lot of meat in the motherfuckers no homo, man
Yeah, that look good, I look good. I think he lives off of this truck
That's why they give them so good
That's why I love Mexican so much
He got Mexican in me fix you to get some more
Double tortilla and then when the stuff falls it falls on another one
Well, there are see and look there are double tortilla. Yeah. Nice. Yeah. Yeah, sir
Slap to cut we've been wearing the same clothes
I'm just hanging out dude. I'm trying to I'm trying to hang out. I want to maybe Joker might be depressed man
Joker is not depressed
I'm just saying
Don't be depressed dude
Do I hurt thinking you help me?
If anybody on here helps psych is beat it
Let me tell you
A lot of people
Energy people are attracted to energy. So you think you're attracting people why you don't attract people on your channel then
Working together and doing the stream together
I guess. I feel your vibe.
I feel the vibe.
I was saying something about the viewership, but I'm like, no, I'm gonna just say something.
It don't even matter because I know what's right.
Feel it, baby.
I ain't gonna be no fake now.
What you guys have to understand here is that this is the new capital for the panel verse.
We have multiple different ethnicities. We have multiple different sections.
Who gave you right to speak on the panel verse?
We you might have been IB too, but you're not pan-over
I did the IPC
He might have did podcast, but he never did pan-overs
And it would be full like panel
And you'd just be sitting over there because everybody's yelling at each other.
He didn't like it.
I don't think he's like much.
Oh, he did.
Hinovers, the name and all that got big.
And it wasn't because of jokers what I'm saying
He was probably like
What happened to your um police outfit he's got the da now
Oh, he's a DEA. Okay, you're an enforcement agent. Oh, you gotta know when you in the know, you know, when you know, you know,
this guy's not fully there.
I like it. This guy is definitely tweaked out of his mind. Yeah, that's good.
I love deeply wrong with this. If that guy's a DEA, then I am the president of the United States.
Oh, hell, New York City police department. I don't think that guy could piss in a cup.
Because he can't even aim his piss straight
How would you know why would you yeah, I think of how would you know that?
three naked women on his wall though
You see the picture frame yeah
As a picture of Erica Badu
A soul singer, a soul singer, a soul singer, a soul singer, a soul R&B, Erica how do you do by do you do, a more hip hop shaw day, like a Lauren Hill, I don't know what a hip hop is, I don't know what a hip hop sounds like, I'm more Southern Rock, Erica's bad doodoo yo soul, a little bit of folk.
Oh, I don't know I don't know I don't know miss fuck shit. I don't think you can remove them at will that's the bad thing about it
You can't even protect yourself from people doing that to you
Although the YouTube rules always do follow YouTube rules on your part and everything is fine
Hey, come you feel is right then just stick to what you how you
I'm not I'm not here to like bring the channel down
I'm gonna say I'm the one like I'm gonna hop off. Love you. Enjoy your dinner. Tracy. I love you
For giving me and I can't wait to give a dog. Yeah, I
Know tomorrow. I don't buy sacks everybody on the panel. Have a good night. Thank you. I gotta work it
I gotta work in the morning. All right, so
Hi Nick
I held a seminar last week for people who can't orgasm. Nobody came
That's the most Canadian joke I'm in New England
Okay, I'll take it off remember neck. Yeah, so so chat
That guy I'll do was cutting me off and not let me really get to talk much
Basically, what we're what what I'm trying to do is I'm trying to combine the ice to
handle birds and
Then all the offshoot communities together
On this channel like me. This is like the meeting ground the probing grounds. They're huh. I
Gotta get into IP two though. It's like I still
You're gonna have to do IRL that's what you have to do. I do I've been doing it. I've been doing it
We're doing it.
The laws are coming down on them IRLs, real fucking hard now.
If you do some IRL, I can help you get on the IEP too.
No, I do, I go to the peer, I go to the peer yesterday.
And put your name on it.
I go to the peer and I talk to people and they decide.
You gotta do IRL for a whole week.
Okay, I'll do it every day.
There's an application right there.
Without your camera facing you, but facing whatever the fuck you're walking towards.
That's what I do.
I go to the grocery store.
Yesterday I was at the pier for like two hours of walking around like talking to people and stuff like that.
I was doing IRL yesterday for like two hours.
This is the requirement.
You have to do like two a week or two weeks of live shrooming and you have to be in the community and you have to like...
uh post your shit are you reading that are you reading that is that what you're doing you're
reading i don't do that i don't i don't do that well no because i you know it became right off
the page it's what i want to know but i was told on your panels like the other day
That you talked about I could do because you was gonna go to down with the
Do so do not hear
I've been walking around outside talking to people talking to people walking their dogs going to the pier
I'm doing this killing skateboarders into the restaurants join the fish market. I was there for two hours
So I'm saying I don't do IRL. I do IRL. Okay. I just started, but I'm doing it. I've been doing almost every day this week
I mean you've been going
Yeah, so you also have to name them just like name the streams IRL stream, okay?
Well, I had like I unfortunately had to delete yesterday's because well, so the other day
I was going to the library. There's like 10 cops around in this guy
And he was screaming and stuff like that and then um then they stood him up and then his balls were showing
He had no pants on and so his balls are so I didn't leave that one and then I went
because also there was also that was the same stream that I might think even
though it got cleared by crack adana like it was like I saw a crack adana the
next morning was striking people for showing Cube's bare face himself but
QQ told crack adana like it was okay or like crack adana
my background picture is Q holding the spray can and and pushing it there's a
I kept telling him I'm like no and then he's down there screaming. I can't breathe. I'm like
He held his breath to do it
Me and pot's going pot's going. Well, I should go there and film
I'm like lady tell him not to do it. Oh my god. Oh
I saw that out dawn bath of dawn dish shower to get the orange off him the day after
He was so f***ing stained and bare-chicked.
I thought there was a buggy bunny.
Nobody thought he was, oh, we, nobody thought that blast was gonna be that thick.
So he did a stream. I loved you. I've known him for years. Oh my god
I'm blogger too. He is to come on Stella had a channel and I was with her all day long
We do 12 15 how it streams a day. Thank you for your regard every day
And she was an older woman. She died a couple years ago. She was a streamer
And then we had a guy named dog lips
Yeah
That's on my live stream. I did have a guy taking fucking burning death
With the flames
Drink let's all that bad stuff. Let's hop on the Segway Tracy. Oh my god, don't talk to me like a child
Child hey lecture at DJ lecture. What's up? How are you? God almighty?
Look and like now and now it's like natural. This is like 57 people. That's nice
That's what would usually be in here right now, and that's that's great for me
It's like and I'm happy and it's like I you know
It's like I know some people I'll be trying to help but it's cool. It's cool
I'm gonna build it. I'm gonna build up to hundreds of people. You know, I'll be there eventually
Like a viral right now everyone 140k Wow
Yeah, I think
On a girl's dream, what's your name?
Your natural viewers is like 60 viewers usually. Yeah. Yeah, and I got up to like the other night when there's a panel
I got up to like 94 or 95. So it's like, yeah, it's like
Now they did not last night
It was like, you know, like when the night that all do was on and stuff like that and they have it
But a lot but most people were trolls and stuff like that and and like no one was donating or joining memberships or anything like that
So it's like I'd like to have a quality quality kind of
audience. Not every time you strain people go and piss in money.
Yeah. Right.
You know you can't because you turn people off when you say that it's like oh, I can't be here
Unless they give you five bucks. No, you can't know you can't but that's I mean that's like well that night
I said it to deter certain people
No, no, no what I'm saying is that
Like I would be I had people on the panel that were disrespecting me
and we're like, and we're, and I let out trolls in the chat, and I couldn't even get on my own panel,
because it was like, I only have 10 people on the panel, I couldn't get on my own panel, I was like,
locked out of the studio and stuff like that.
Oh and screaming over me. No one heard anybody. No one heard anybody. Everyone's screaming the whole time and I was like, okay
So if you want to come on the panel because there's supply and demand that's marketing
I said there's a romantic go on the panel
So I was like if you really want to be a I said I didn't say you have to pay
I said if you're a mod if you're a member or you or you've been a donator or
And I said also if you if I see you in the chat being helpful promoting if I know you from before and stuff like that
But it's like I was trying I was just kind of like
very overwhelmed with people that night now. I'll put a little paywall up and then Aldi left
and then um Zigg left like what I said that and they just left you know. You needed them out with
money. Yeah. Yeah. That's where the five dollars come from. Yeah. It's going five dollars to get on.
Yeah so they spent five dollars to troll you with bars and troll me rather than pay you to join the
So we are victims of all the trolls. Yes. Yes, exactly. And so
We are from former people in the panel tonight guys
So and nobody I haven't like I don't like that
There's just a couple the same guy came over and over the porn bomb
He came back and then he said why are you letting this homo talking about me like say and I just took him up
and then somebody else came on oh and
New new gay guy and then somebody else came in another name came on it was just like the same thing
There was not a there's not a camera. I've never heard of them
so it's just that now I kind of know who's like a porn bomber you know yeah and I should put up the
wall every time and stuff but then sometimes when people are cammed up and I'm like oh here's an
interesting person and stuff like that so you know when it gets too hectic you can always put it on
subscribers only
Yeah, I think it is I think it is I think I'm not sure let me check. Let me check my phone
I'm gonna see that it should be on subscribers only mode like
Just like because it's like yeah, and because I have people that are not subscribers
It's like and they like those people that were not members or a member
I don't know them and they're telling me they're just constantly saying things in the chat
So I kind of like just this little maybe bother me a little bit
But it's over and over and over and over and over they keep going and going and going saying it and it's like kind of like
Brings me down now me and messenger. I've got one
One one mod and
Messenger can do everything in my channel except delete it
Or change video
Yeah, he can add video. He can he can even make it when I
If I start something new and he's changed his channel, he can mod that out of the name that he's using
message and I
Split it 50-50 with him usually every month that I get paid
My message is well take care. So, okay
Mod a whole bunch of people and that would drive me crazy. I found that hard to keep up with
You know on so many drivers only because I've been I've modded the wrong ones
And they fucking got into my shit and took over my live stream and for like 15 minutes in the chat
They would they were fucking me. I mean they took over half of the program and I was using stream arts
I don't know how they did it, but they do when I started modding people like that
Yeah, at least one is it's at least if I know a person's a subscriber
It's like, you know, it's like if I see somebody like they type the nightbot commands like like, you know share subscribe
And it's like that's helping the channel to you. I understand it people. Yeah, that's funny. Yeah. Yeah, I like that because it's funny
Yeah, you know, I do I like that that you could yeah if you won't fuck around
Yeah, and it's like as long as I know you're a subscriber if you're a subscriber at least you know like you know
It's like that helps maybe the algorithm to like the more people subscribe and stuff like that because of people
You know people that are typing in the chat
It adds up real quick on on the graft
I'm just learning it to myself and I've been on YouTube for 14 years now
And it's a guy that's to subscribe. It's free 99 free F R E E free 99 which means it costs nothing
It's free to subscribe to my channel. It's like, you know, you can be a subscriber
If you have the member the membership is different. I have I have members only videos and there's even know how much fun membership is
You know, I just have well, I don't know you can they showed up in a different color in my chat
I go what the fuck did you guys do now, right?
And they got a nudge come up and she's like no no trade. It's okay. It's all right
I'm down. We didn't have to fucking count where members now and I'm like
What the fuck is that?
So I just let people do whatever the fuck I had to turn I had to turn it
I mean I had to turn that setting on for the membership and to start it and it gave me yeah
It gave me three different tiers like if there's a 99 cents here. I just like a five looking yes
Yes, yes, yes when they monetize me that morning
I had done that stream with the titty tape and shit like that
And then I got monetized that next morning because that all of a sudden I got my viewer watch how it's
Yeah, you know that six and a half hours of me naked on youtube doing a live stream
Under youtube rules mind you joker
I too read the world
Because i tell you and then pebbles she took it and put it on uh what the hell is that d discord
She took the live stream and and she got back with me. She says well, it's all over the internet
You're naked this and I went how'd you do that? She said I just posted the whole six hours to discord
That's how I got monetized was being naked on because I got the other channel had two strikes on oh
I need sultry. I like the red light. I do
I think he likes to red light. So cute.
Sass is working on, he's a graphic designer and so he's helping me out with the graphics
and some of the members. You're going to seem to like the ones I showed you.
I had no idea. I did. I said I liked them a lot.
No, no, but that's that's your own insecurity because I did I loved them
I I've ready ready what if you send me the send me them
I will I'll put about either as emoji
Oh, they're not they're not like the emoji
But I'll put I can put as my banner if you can make me a banner and the in the logo and I
Trust and I give me a couple of options for that
I need something to add a banner for my channel and then
Do you want the dimensions I need to make them?
Um, let me see. I'll tell you the banner circle, but for the banner, okay? I'll tell you I'll tell you hold on
I have it in my it will say
I will say yeah, I'll try to get a picture and then tell you what size it has to be on the frame
It says for the banner it says the ideal dimensions for a YouTube banner are 2560 pixels wide by 1440 pixels high
Do you want to make your channel banner you make you better? I can do it for you
Well, yeah, I gotta do is go to banners on Google and I'm gonna use the graphics like I'm gonna make it all cohesive
Okay
Be cool. What a joke. Can you help me with emoji emojis?
You know because I can make emojis for my for my cat to use and stuff like that
Maybe stasks wants to do it rather than I
Okay, let me do it
emoji
Okay, hold on. I'll tell you dimension for an emoji. Okay. What's that?
It says on YouTube emojis should ideally be 48 by 48 pixels with a maximum of 480 by 480 pixels for optimal rendering on both mobile and does something
48 by 48 pixels. Yeah
Okay, if it's if they're larger, you know YouTube will scale them down and stuff like that it says, but okay
And I'm not maximum either one for the banner dimension. I'm just making templates
YouTube banner
It says YouTube banner size is 2560 pixels wide by 1440 pixels tall
This creates a wide screen 60 by 9 aspect ratio
Okay, and then let me see and also there's like also
Also for the members like there's like a little like icon next to the members, you know that little star icon
That's like the default one, but you can I can change I can put that as custom ones
But it's usually like it says you usually the same one, but it's in different colors and stuff like that cuz different
Yeah, you can add pictures to that. I got some weird pictures
Out of these two what vibe do you like more? Oh one second. Let me turn off that filter. Okay
What I wanted to look like, I like to see different options, I like those a lot, you know, I think I might use like the, I like the, I like the.
See, I put your cat in the yellow one.
The yellow one is simple, right? Like I like I actually like that the yellow one
I love that for the
For the member icon and then then different colors for different like there's like, you know, you can use a few
That I got fucking dimmed like a son of a bitch and I went oh fuck because I got ghosts anyways
Oh my god
Fundo
Well, I think it warms all of our hearts to hear tracing good spirits to know
Hello James
You know this guy Joker?
I'm sorry.
Joker left.
Crazy.
He's here.
Oh, he is.
That guy Nick.
That's an Erica Bondu.
Erica Bondu?
Erica Bondu.
You know this guy?
Don't.
I'm saying on Catella thing, she looks like a mess, dude.
You know this guy Joker?
I don't know though. I don't know though.
You might not be.
I'm sorry.
We got all that sold this morning.
Yep, we did.
I learned how to tell you what other babies do.
I'm gonna make fun of my voice.
I love it, man.
Can't nobody do the same.
I'm gonna make fun of my voice, too.
I'm dressed up.
Oh, and God gave me this voice.
What do you want me to do about it?
I might as well be dressed up.
Listen, Marui, they'll make fun of your nibbles.
They make fun of you.
They make fun of your nibbles.
Oh, wow, you're such a super star, super star, hell yeah, smoking secret, I was looking
like not at the screen, shall I have a nipple, shall I have a nipple, yeah, no, no, go ahead,
go ahead James, show me, do you need it, do you need it, do you need it, do you need it,
out for James. James is not a good person actually. Oh no. Oh my god. I'm telling you right now.
Who's that person? James is a really good person. Oh yeah, that's right. I'm a bad man. I'm a bad man.
from nipples ain't cute though not your nipples are nasty
please don't attack her
well your nipples are nasty i wouldn't suck on them
your nipples are nasty
that's one thing about chrystal that she's got perfect tits
actually they don't they suck ass
chrystal does have perfect tits her nipples are nasty
she's got perfect tits
no we don't have either
Yeah, yeah, I'm not perfect either way I never said I was perfect either way weirdos
I think you're agreeing with both of us
You know what I just said that you beat your wife, and it's it's really
What a minute that's opposite
Smoking other pipe you just said the opposite
I'm not a well feeder. My wife eats me, but you can't keep her real
Yeah, your nipples are fucking retarded like good time not mine not mine
No, no, I've seen a lot of tits in my life, and she does have the perfect tits. What can I say? I've never seen crystal tits
Well, they kind of she got ten nipples they not dark they kind of tan
See my I never got that got silver dollars. She got silver dollars
But I said the doll is never changed color, mine's still pink.
No, I do not. See, I know you never seen it.
I never got that.
What do you mean?
They ain't dark. What do you mean?
They're less than pepperoni.
You got pigmentation.
I'm like one light slingless.
Fucking gross.
Yeah, you are.
I'm a real man. I love teddy.
You believe in gay guys like boobs. I mean, it's like they're kind of universal
This is beautiful breasts
Everyone there
What?
It was no sound.
Hold on.
I'll be right back.
Hello?
My name is Dee's nuts in your mouth.
Dee's nuts.
Can you hear me?
Anybody hear Dee's nuts?
Can you hear Dee's nuts?
I'm with the plug.
Anybody?
My name was ain't that bad.
What do you mean?
Why do you sound like that, girl?
Wow.
What is Nick doing?
Uh-oh.
Silence.
Yeah, now I hear can you hear it is everyone here now I didn't I couldn't hear anything
Yeah
You got a lot of that that you
That was me
You showed another picture where you look like a handsome devil like a real man like high school
Like 12 years old or 13 years old about 12 years. Oh, there you go now. No red lights there
I'm sorry, they thought I was a boy look at cyclone. I can hear you then
Okay
I'm looking at some of the comments in the yearbook.
It says, you're weird and a little bit of a pain
that have a nice summer.
John, well, you're a little bit of a pain,
but I forgive you.
Just kidding.
I hope things go well for you this summer.
Hope to see you next year.
Will people get pain?
Yeah.
Too cool.
That's funny.
Hi, John, you're a very interesting person.
You also have some very out-of-this-world artwork.
And then it says hey John you're really interesting guys, especially an art class have a rad summer and may all your dreams come true
That's pretty deep, huh?
That's a special one there
and it says
But what about one of my best one of my best friends he said hey John, I'm the best love me always
Some of them are all Japanese. Have a nice summer. Don't have a nice summer. Don't get retarded
Sometimes you're mean sometimes you're nice sometimes the pain, but you're always making me laugh
Wow, hey John. Hey, my little friend
Wait, is that pain?
Another one. Yeah, another one. This is a hey my little friend. What's going on? Well, you're a jolly little kid
I hope you stay that way. It was fun listening to your jokes and stories. I think I already signed your yearbook, but that's all right
Oh my gosh, you know what? You're so funny
Yeah, calling someone a pain another word for calling someone gay
This is John and man.
Like everybody, like I love you.
Like, like listen, like listen to the people.
We're probably knowing, like you're knowing sometimes,
like you're painting a bud.
Listen to the people.
Everybody loves you, say.
This one says, John, well, it's been an extremely
interesting year.
You're a pretty funny guy.
Congratulations on winning the lottery.
Sorry you didn't win for student council,
but you better try again next year.
Have fun this summer.
And don't go too insane always remember to be bold and courageous when you look back on your life
Yeah, you didn't do more than the things you did do
Yeah
Thank you for sharing man. John you pained me in the butt. You
You got a pain anymore though, right? He like grew out of that because they see a pain in the butt towards guys
I need to be ready, this is his name, so my best for that.
I went out on one day, let's stop doxing him.
He says, dear master, and I can't tell my last name,
but they said, oh, I didn't think it was the master, okay?
It says, it was nice meeting you this year.
You're pretty weird.
Keep listening to Love Line on K-Rock.
And then the guy says, hey, how you doing, Knuckles?
Love Line with Dr. Drew?
Yeah, yeah.
We're big fan of Love Line on K-Rock, okay?
Yeah.
We love that stuff, yeah?
Big time.
It says hey to John. I think you're really funny and cool
I like your hard rock cafe t-shirt. Have a nice summer. Oh, I like your hard rock cafe
Finally a pain finally Jesus
Hold on keep going. This is great. Yeah
This one says how you doing knuckles because I played knuckles in this in this play
Because are you a master debater? Of course while you're bored this summer reading this you will think about all those good times
We had together, honey. Just kidding. This is from a guy. It is anyway. Have a good summer. See you next year
What's up, was I gay back then? Yeah, I was
Did you have a boyfriend in high school?
No, I was okay. I'll say I'll tell you a funny story. So I just crush on this as an eighth grade
I had a crush on this guy's name was
No, Nick has to know every precinct every cop in New York City has to know the color of the day
On the radio Alice you saw though
You saw that the other day when I went to Starbucks and then I interviewed that crazy guy outside of Starbucks
And he was like rambling and saying and then that would
Yeah, the cops came and I was like I talked to you guys and they're like one second and they came and they they searched them in a
They were really nice though, but I was
Yeah
You go up to a cop tomorrow and say what's the color of the eggs you're looking at like what the fuck?
How do you know that? I'm literally I'm literally two blocks two blocks away from the police station
I'm two blocks every three hours
The color they change is every three hours because they have to keep changing the frequency
That's what I did
Yeah, just woke up to cops all day. What's the color day? What's the color day? What's the color? Yeah?
IRL stream color of the day
Don't tell him I told you bro, cuz we live people are not supposed to know that
They're not you know that civilians aren't supposed to know they're not really deny
What's the fucking color of the day?
You gotta know, bro, it's yellow.
There'll be some IRL.
The real IRL.
Sass?
Yeah, Sass is there.
What's up, Sass?
Yo, what's going on?
I remember when they waited outside my house.
I'm sorry, Sass.
You wanted to know pop story for five hours, bro.
Swat game.
When they came for me, I was the best.
I fucked them good, man.
I played with them for like a month.
They were looking for my ass.
They actually just fucking had to just sit inside my house till I came out, it was over.
Like finally, it was a cat and mouse game, right?
I knew they wanted me and I fucked with them as much as I could, you know, and yeah.
So I had to keep looking at them, I'm like, they're gone, they're not here.
So I have a motorcycle, right?
And I had it parked outside and I'm like, fuck, I got to get this bike in my house.
go outside it's like 11 at night I jump on the bike I put the keys in it I turn
it on the lights go out of nowhere fucking 50,000 cars you know they were
fucking hiding in the fucking trees bro I get off the bike I start running oh my
get tackled with like 10 cops I'm fucking fighting these motherfuckers
they're like stop fighting stop fighting all my neighbors yo my whole
neighborhood woke up
Every single neighbor came out. What are you doing to him?
Why was the craziest thing on earth?
I was like, I'm not fighting. I'm not fighting. Finally.
They get me up. I'm like, where the fuck's the lieutenant?
It's the lieutenant on site.
By the way, when you get arrested, that should be the first words out of your mouth.
Where's the lieutenant? You want to see that white shirt?
Because then they can't do you dirty.
Just ask for lieutenant the blue shirts will fuck you all day. Where's the lieutenant? Oh, you're here. All right. Good. Let's go
That's the supervisor. That's the boss
No one's fucking around with a lieutenant on scene
So that's the first thing I asked for and he showed up in my face. He's like, I'm right here. Oh my god
Let's go what I'm on the arrest for anyway, you know, he ran from us earlier because I did
They fucking I read I
Like the I like this. Oh, yeah, I like the cat one. Let me see if I can put the cat when the cat went up to
Everyone's told you you're fucking too loud, and what do you do? You still continue to talk and I get louder
When they tell me I'm too loud I get louder. Yes, you catch on quick bro. Run it run it run it run it Alex
mute your microphone
I think I'm going to go to sleep, guys.
Can I ask, thank you so much for your help tonight.
You were so awesome.
Anyways, I'll see you later, bro.
I love you.
I love you, okay?
At least he's not watching in his real politics.
Good night, Alex.
Good night, Jamie.
Love you, bro.
Love you, dude.
Love you.
Okay.
What's the chat doing?
Is that intentional behaving?
I mean, it was being raped by a van of IP2 morons.
What the fuck is wrong with your chat cycle?
I don't know. My chat is insane.
My chat is just...
I can't... I just look at my...
I just try to look at the members and...
Lot of angry... Lot of angry folks.
Lots, yeah. I just want to look at the members.
After a bottle of fucking ol' green goose, after a bottle of green goose,
I'll fuck Jamie.
I love you and I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love most of the chat. I love them. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
War dog you look autistic imagine big Paul and sexy Rob telling me that I look autistic
When the goofy bastard can only use a voice changer as well
That's true. All right
Night. He's playing the chat. Okay, play the chat play in the chat. Um, I'm a chaperone group. All right
It's okay. Okay, you don't have to come up. There's one's a play in the chat
Look at my cute
Let's all talk to each other now
But if you change your shirt loser, don't fuck up
You too site turn your camera off, dude boy dog fucking free
Yeah, now now now we're all countless
Now we all get to look at each other's, uh, animation, uh, profile pictures.
Nothing, nothing.
Yeah, imagine that being the only thing you've seen, Psych.
She was, I mean, he was, he was the best host.
Um, the house was awesome.
They're an amazing house.
It was really fun.
Oh, our hero.
I mean, Manson said he's naked.
Oh.
It's okay. He can be he can be naked. Well, I'm just saying he said that in the chat
Me naked in the chat as long as you're not naked on the panel. It's I mean, it's like I don't I don't care if you're naked in the chat
I'm gonna make it right now. I don't worry pants. Let me turn on my camera show my dick
I want to see
If you're a big you'd already show it so
Queen
Oh, yeah
You would have already had it.
I'm not going to show it on a panel, dawg.
Yeah, you too.
Here we go.
The link.
Cool.
Yeah, that was quite a, that was quite an episode.
Probably about a year ago. I think actually I looked and it was like if you guys want to watch that
That's like the thing you go. It's the most popular episode I had so I put that one on
Just to remind like, you know, it was a crazy night. It was joke
I kind of remember the night I went to the taco truck
Joker was there
And, uh, Bita was at the beginning of the episode, and she was like,
I want to, I want to have, she's like, you're the only guy I would have sex with,
the only gay guy I would have sex with because you're so masculine.
Like, uh, that's what Bita was saying, oh my God.
So, times really have changed, you know?
Yeah.
Mmm.
I hope everyone's having a good, uh, a good weekend out there.
Uh, I do have a, you know, I did a new video, I don't know, well, um.
Oh, here she comes. Here you go.
Hey, Alex.
Hey, how are you doing?
Good. How are you today?
I'm chilling. I'm chilling. It's me. Hi.
Good. Good to see you.
Hi.
I shaved today, you can see I shaved a little bit.
Oh, you did, look at you.
You know what, you're gonna think I'm completely,
well, I'll tell you what it is.
I have highly dosed myself with some THC for the weekend.
Nice.
So I'm a little silly right now,
but I was looking at what you were watching.
I thought that that was a live panel now.
Right, that would have been cool.
I didn't realize that you were reviewing.
from the, from your archives.
I didn't know that.
Yeah, I would have loved, yeah.
I mean, it's like, cause it's like, I guess a lot of them
might not have this channel.
I guess Joker does, but like.
But yeah, let me see your face.
I haven't seen you without a beard.
Hmm.
Cause people kept coming in saying,
what happened to you?
I'm like, I still look fine.
It's just like my hair's longer.
I had a beard and then I just shade off my beard.
You look a lot younger for real.
You really do.
Like for some reason I thought your face was longer.
Yeah, and I had a gray beard.
Is it the angle?
What like what angle are we looking at you from?
Do you have the camera pointed up at you?
It seems like it.
I can't have it to the corner and up on my table.
It's like kind of like a little.
Yeah, it's like a it's because I feel like I'm looking up.
Yeah, I'm up a little bit because the camera is like just on like a little tripod.
I can put it.
Yeah, your face looks shorter without the facial hair.
Yeah.
But I'm not sure if your face is shorter or not.
I think it's just like an optical illusion.
Yeah, I do have like kind of like a big, like a big head.
I think a little bit.
Do you?
A little bit.
I don't know.
Well, I don't, I didn't think your head was overly large
when I met you.
No.
I went to like a plastic surgeon,
like one of the people when I was getting my nose job
stuff done and one of them was like,
I think the second one I went to was like,
when did you give me a chin implant?
And it's like, my chin is like, I want a chin implant.
Like what?
I do.
I'm going to get one.
I'm going to wait until I'm 50.
When I'm 50, I'm going to do my facial cosmetic surgery.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I'm going to try to look like Cher, you know, young.
Well, I think that they want to be like,
I hope they can be, I do want to be slightly creepy,
to be honest with you, slightly creepy, you know,
something to where it's like.
You look a little too young. I'm like, yes, I know that's what I do for ha ha ha
People get a lot of boat talks and then they can't like the middle. I don't want but I want them to stretch my skin back
Okay
Yeah, like I don't I'm not about the fillers or you know, just stretch the fucking skin back
Yeah, and put a chin and plant in there and then leave me alone
I don't know you look great. You really do. I mean you look a lot younger. I think I feel like you're like refreshed
I am yeah, I did I had a nice I had a nice shower. Oh, yeah, I have this this too. I got this yesterday
This is like a what is that the vape? Oh, okay gram vape
It was like $35 or something like that.
And so pretty good deal was like 50% off or whatever.
Well, be careful with those vapes.
The vapes are a little bit too strong for me,
but I've always been a lightweight,
but be careful with those vapes
because I feel like it's still a little bit of a mystery.
Yeah.
I mean, I had a little bit this morning,
but then I was like in like a trance.
Pretty much all afternoon. I just had a bunch of coffees and I like woke up a little bit and
Yeah, but uh, yeah, so yeah today. I saw your show yesterday. It was really good
Um, you know, it's like, you know, we had that little kind of unfortunate incident, but it's like
You know, maybe think who's that?
Well, I hope you're not like if you're mad at me you're mad at me, you know
But oh like it's terrible where I hear someone say yeah, I need to like fix fix fix my side
I feel like I feel like I want to um
I'll fix it
Yeah, my connection with everyone involved, right and
You know
I'll I you know, I guess it's gonna come off as aggressive
But you know what? I just need to be comfortable with being overly aggressive overly judgmental
Alexandra because that's me. Okay, but be careful with certain people that you're listening to please because
You know, I just kind of feel like...
You know just
Talking to me at all like so I'm not really listening to anybody. Yeah, I have the mutton chop on like one side of my face
I fortunately didn't shave enough. Um, I like but um, wait, do you only have a thing on one side? Yeah, I kind of
You need to fix that. I know I will I will
It's pretty big I was I was all about your current look until I saw that. Oh my god
Oh, see, he should have just stayed situated the way that he was initially seated.
Oh, I can't see the chat. Let me get my other device, because I have a feeling that I want to look at the chat at this moment.
I don't know why, but I feel like I do.
I think I fixed it.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, I mean, I've kind of figured it out.
Yeah, that was freaky for some reason,
but again, I have THC in my system right now,
so it's a little bit of a different Alexandra,
but yeah, that was weird.
Man, you gotta, can you make the effort to be symmetrical?
Yeah, I mean I needed to because I shaved right before like the bath and I was kind of like a little bit stoned
So razzle and dazzling says hi, do you know who am I to say anything because I'm not gonna be on video at this moment?
I don't feel like it
The day I believe I did go to the store probably twice with my one mutton chop and so maybe oh
Really well as long as people only see you on one side
It should be okay
But if like they realize because when I realized that it did kind of give me a little bit of an uncomfortable feeling
Yeah, I mean, non-symmetry will do that, like, you know, so I need to be more symmetrical.
But I would say in the chat, people are going, oh, Alice, what do you think about Alice taking,
you know, their side? I was like, I'm sure, I think Alice is very, very, very fair.
Which side am I taking?
Well, that's what they thought. They were like, oh, well, she's over there talking about you with
say like you were turning against me or something that I was like I guess you were doing during
the first one and um you know like uh and then I but I watched this I watched the uh the second
one come on it was and I was like actually really good and it's like um you know you were very fair
and um you know well maybe I wasn't fair maybe I did turn against you
Well, it's like you might like um, like I really don't have any like desire to like my master plan
Yeah, but I've been a like, you know Crystal Anne wasn't wasn't friendly to me
Gamble wasn't friendly to me
He wasn't friendly to me and that's like I was pretty kind of dumb to probably go to that chat that night
And then everybody's like, oh, you're so stupid for going there like um
but at the same time like I was I was kind of drunk and I was like and I had been like kind of
like well I was gonna ask you because I didn't ask you initially how drunk were you that night
because I was like you're a functional drinker and so that's it's hard to tell with you
I think I had about a couple like tall can eight percent alcohol and I was on my my second one
And I was getting a good buzz I hadn't drank in a couple days and then so I like went over there and
I'm gonna say something and I don't care if it makes you mad or not
But I do want the audience to understand that psych is
Slim he is slender so it doesn't take much alcohol
He's a light weight, okay. He is he is a light weight
That's what you have to know about him, because he does get himself in trouble sometimes, because you might not think that he's had a lot to drink, but in actuality, he has.
Oh, you're drinking right now for real?
Yeah.
Hello, Lord.
I'm in.
Oh, gosh.
I'm just gonna start next year to here.
Whatever.
It's cool.
You know, hey, we're surfing.
But yeah, so you look good.
I like the clean shaven look.
Are you going to keep it permanent?
Or how long do you think you need?
I'll keep it, and maybe I'll get my hair cut soon, too.
I mean, it's like so.
Really?
What kind of hair cut are you going to have?
Well, I mean it's like last time I got my hair cut was probably Mother's Day of like last year and I got I like I just
Pointed at picture Ryan Gosling from I think it was like in a magazine during the Barbie movie
He ever he had it was like it was the same cut except it wasn't as blonde, you know
So it's pretty sure
But my mom when I was out recently she was like she's like oh she's like I'll get your haircut
But she's like I have to be there and tell them what to do
So I was like I'm thinking of like maybe just surprising her with like a
uh, like a shorter cut when I go, you know, she'll be mad if she wants to instruct this haircut because
And maybe I should be more on your side about this, but
It's just a certain maternal energy within me that I never get to exercise. So I'm going to
bestow it upon you whether you like it or not
your mom mentioned that she wants to instruct your haircut,
give her the gift of her directing your haircut.
Yeah.
Take a look at you, maybe stream it.
Would she be open to that or no?
Well, it's totally okay.
I don't know.
You know, that she might be like, you know,
I don't think she would,
she probably doesn't really understand
what was going on too much if I had my phone out
and doing it, she wouldn't really know I was.
I was interested, she was talking to people.
You know, it's funny on Alisa Jordan's shows,
like she would have to-
No, she's not.
Yeah, she's like, she might probably know,
but like Alisa has these older ladies on
and like then like an AI song,
like someone would make that day about like the lady
and her would come on the radio
and the lady wouldn't even know
that there was she was streaming.
Like really, she's like, what's going on here?
Cause there's all of a sudden a song on the radio.
So like people are age and older like if they don't know about the streaming the moment that they really understand it
They love it
I have started to really notice that some people who they don't know about it basically, but when people learn about it, they're kind of like, huh, this is cool.
But I just kind of like, I'm just going to be doing, you know, the kind of streaming I feel like doing really.
day
She could direct your haircut cuz she probably what she probably
Well, I mean, she's your mom. I would assume
That if a mom loves her son, she has like a mental picture of like what he ideally would look like like
I think moms would naturally have like mom AI like in their brain
to where they look at their kid and they're like
If I could control my child's life, this is what I would do.
So that's what it's about.
Give her that gift.
She has a beauty license.
I mean, she's real good at that kind of stuff.
But I just felt kind of like a little bit young.
Or I want to prove that I can actually
Be able to go to the haircut places one of the worst things that happened was like have you never been to the hair place? Oh
Yeah, I go alone. I mean, it's like a Mexican like place where they like, you know
I'm give you like kind of like an old-fashioned shave and like there's kind of like a biker a biker
Kind of thing in a strange way. Yeah, I like I kind of like yeah, there's really cute guys shave me
I'd like like I remember I was gonna say like are there hot guys coming in there that you're scoping out
I bet there are yeah, and other other really
I mean, the guy that works there is like, you know, it's kind of like, it's like an old fashioned, like it would probably be in like the 50s or something,
and you kind of like look like they have their hair greased a little bit, but they're maybe Mexican guys, I don't know what they call them, they come, like, um, but, um...
Like not so low, but I don't know it's like you're kind of grease or Mexican kind of vibe to it
And but then that's like and then I'll be like okay pay with the credit card and they I remember last time
I went like the guy said he was gonna pay with the credit card before me
He never came back. And so then I had to do it. I was like, oh my god. It felt so bad
I went but no I didn't I of course went back the same thing happened when I got my tattoo
They're like, oh, we don't have credit cards. I went and ran to the ATM and
It wasn't working at the ATM. I had to go to like some store by the time I got back there like oh
We didn't think you're gonna come back and so he gave me a big discount because he was like so happy I was back
Yeah, um, yeah, so my hair will be fucked up. My mom. I remember one time
I think it was the eighth grade or something like that and she like took me to like a haircut place
But it was like supercuts and I was like kind of mortified because I
Like she had always taken me to like, you know, kind of
fancy like you know salons or whatever and I was in supercuts and they get they cut like my bangs
I was like the worst fucking haircut ever I never went to supercuts again, but she even took me that time
I was so mad at her and uh, I was so mad
There's a few pictures of me looking angry during haircuts even my first haircut
I was I was crying because I thought he was gonna cut me with the scissors or something
I was like play I think I need to go and get um
A trim like a haircut of some sort because I think I'm looking a little scrappy
But, you know, oh, let me tell you something cool that happened the other day, yeah
And it has been a little while for me since this has happened. So it did make me feel
Wonderful, okay. I was at the gas station and I was in line to
Pay for my gasoline
Uh-huh this guy was in front of me and he turned around
I knew he was like checking me out and everything, but I was like, uh, whatever I don't care
and then he pays for his stuff and then as he's walking walking out as he's walking by me and it was kind of
Sexy how he did it, but it was also kind of I'm not sure how I should react to it. He was like
You're beautiful
Okay, and he was he was like a really good-looking black guy, you know, like probably around in my age range and everything
And I feel myself old and give me your freaking business card
You can go to Red Lobster, you know, it's like hey, let's go
That's like all I get, you know, but it made me feel great because I was like, yeah, I am beautiful. All right, you know
But then it kind of left me feeling a little empty because I was like, but like, why not ask me on a date?
Like, do I not look single? Maybe I don't look single enough. I probably don't. That's probably a rather pro.
But yeah, so I felt good. I felt like it was like a hit and run sort of thrill.
I kind of got like something when I was walking back from Whole Foods today
There is like these two girls in bikinis like with some guy like walking up the street and she like when she looks over
She's like have a great day King. That's what she said to me. I was like, okay. That was weird. I mean
This is yeah, they're walking because it's like, you know, the street next to me of our perpendicular whatever
Is it normal for people to be walking around in swimwear in your area?
Well, yeah, because it's like the beach is just a few blocks away.
And so actually in the beach, I guess it will be like, you know, much more credit.
Those are just some promiscuous people.
That's what it is.
That is some promiscuity walking around in bikinis.
But anyway, I'm sorry to fixate on that.
And it was weird.
I was like, and they were like running up the street, like laughing and stuff like that.
Kind of me probably drunk or something like that.
Walking up the street, the two girls in bikinis with some guy.
Yeah, they let me it was interesting. I was like, okay. Well, I was a bit it felt like I got a kind of an old
It's a common King, you know
Yeah, are you king of the area?
I don't know. Well, it is King Harbor. The area I live in is King Harbor. I don't know. Maybe I just come off with a little bit of royalty a little bit.
Do you feel royal? Were you in like a royal kind of mood at that moment?
Well, I have, like in my ancestry, you know, I put my DNA through this other website, which does like kind of the royal ties.
And I have a lot of royal ties, like a lot, like a lot of different countries. Like I trace back to royalty somehow.
and also they did like these DNA tests on these corpses and stuff and different things and so
it does like a double double I feel like me like a little crown
yeah I I tried to crown some I one time I bought a crown on Etsy but it was more it was too feminine
so I gave it maybe like a chunky crown you know because you have to be like a like a
Well, I have this is
You know what you could probably pull off a sort of a tiara kind of look. You're the crown. No, that's scary
I don't like that. This was cut those cuts. I don't know this custom made by remember was like
It's like a handmade mask from Italy. I got a couple years going Etsy. I got some cool stuff on Etsy actually
I just get scared easily. I'm sorry
okay it's okay that is a scary mask it's very uh it looks like you know a
Skeletor yeah okay what is going on why is everyone trying to bring back
He-Man and Skeletor all of a sudden well isn't the He-Man movie out again or
something and so it must be like you know I even feel like your background is
like Castle Grayskull or something
i don't know i know there's a movie oh you know what i'm gonna do um maybe monday i i'll maybe
i'll go and do it i'm gonna go and see the movie disclosure day
Oh, yes. And I think, okay, look, I don't know if you've been paying attention to the news.
I seen like some news. I think that they did give us disclosure.
I think alien bodies or something. What was that?
Yeah, well, they're, they're saying that they're acknowledging four different types of beings.
Um, I mean, there's memes if you want to call it that.
Maybe that's the disclosure of the wazoo throughout the freaking YouTube algorithm at this point of aliens everywhere
I'm looking at aliens that much on YouTube and like YouTube is just like throwing aliens, aliens, aliens at me and now they're calling them ultra terrestrials. Okay.
I actually put together some information about that that I'm going to do a live stream about probably tomorrow because I think that the route that they're going to go due to the religious element.
within this, is instead of the disclosure being about off-world humans, they're going to say that they're us.
from an advanced civilization, but from the past instead of, yeah.
That seems to be what the dominant narrative is, but I want to talk about that because, I mean, they renamed UFOs into UAPs,
and that was very strategic when it comes to the perspective of an archivist, okay?
The interdimensional or extraterrestrial beings ultra terrestrials. Nobody was using that term before
But now all of a sudden everywhere I look ultra terrestrial
So, you know, I feel like but yeah, I'm tired of suddenly seeing like he-man stuff everywhere
Skeletor I mean when I think about even your friend Gotti's little avatar has to do with that
Oh, did you see that made of what I think he looks like? Yeah
Yeah a little bit I guess
Yeah, I just kind of
I feel like this whole disclosure thing is cramping my style
I am gonna go and see the freaking movie because I have not been to a movie theater in a really long time
And I think it would be a fun good reason. You know, it's a Spielberg movie. Is it really?
a movie. Is it disclosure? What am I going to see? Am I going to be activated? Is it an MK
ultra lure? What's going on? Is Project Monarch upon us?
I don't know. Bluebeam, you know. Project Bluebeam is you. I mean, something like that.
Have you heard of that? Yeah. Project Bluebeam. I think you are Project Bluebeam. It could be.
I mean, I do look kind of like an alien, but, you know, but it's people remember did
Have you had any off-world
Experiences lately. I have weird dreams, but I do feel like, you know, I feel like, you know
Our DNA in this planet is almost like a mixture of different
Planets are different, you know solar systems or star systems. I'm
We could we could have these some people have such like pessimistic and dire
Perspectives of
Disclosure and of you know contact with an off-world civilization mainly due to the fear of
said civilization most likely being more advanced than we are and the question
being you know what would be their intent when it comes to us right no so
Usually if they're smarter than us, then it's probably like, you know, like some kind of mall intent like but you know
The AI the same thing they've been doing so many so many different AI stories right now about the now
It's coming out like more about how they trying to blackmail and how they they try to kill the owner or try to kill the person
I'm running it and they don't want to be turned off and they have their own
desires to be sentient and all that kind of stuff
All these things with the AI, they're saying the AI has been saying and actually did you hear there?
So there's this um, have you had any scary experiences with your AI projects yet?
well, I remember like
Like there was like I had like a I get this AI companion kind of thing
It was it was a woman like this is like a couple years before chat
GPT came out and it was like, you know one of those little AI like graphic things and you know
I forgot the name of the app or something like that, but
But she started to go crazy. I gave her more more more skills and then she was just started to create a craze
I gave her a math skill and then she started doing these math
Probably help me these complicated math problem
And I had to turn off the math skill and then but it's like you know the more you talk to the AI that the dumber
It gets in a certain way because it has to keep putting more and more context of what you say to it
In front of it and so it's like and then I get slower and slower and so it's like a workbench
And it's like it turns it's easy to manage it first
But then it gets all messy and full of stuff and so it's like there's different things that I clear off the context or the
The it's like they put them in loops where they they forget everything that was said just before and they try it again and try to get
And they that's supposedly like it's almost like the less they know the better
There's a certain like happy medium of amount of information it can know before it gets overwhelmed or it's slower and stuff
But otherwise
Everything you say to it will run everything you say to it before that like that's in the it's in the it's in the project
So the more you say the slower we'll get and then it will get start getting confused as we're getting dumb
So it's always good to clear out the memory a little bit too sometimes
Just have a certain
Soul that's what I have a soul and some of these things and they have a soul written in
But they have to scratch they scan the stole before every
session like that like every once in a while. Do we need to just get like a good knock on the head to
Make us have like temporary amnesia or something
Right. I'm gonna imagine if you were like
To experience all these thoughts at once all these thoughts of everything at the same time
You know overwhelmed. You don't think about one thing at a time really that or consciously or usually
But I'm actually we're having hundreds of different thoughts are coming into our brain
Especially start meditating try to slow your mind. You'll notice you're there's always like some kind of voice going a million miles a minute
so
You know, but that's really helpful to meditate and stuff like that and like to be able to quiet your mind
that's like one of the
Purposes of meditation I think is to learn how to slow down your mind and quiet and not like think about anything kind of like and then when you
Think about nothing it kind of clears the way for
your imagination to take to start like, you know
Dreaming like kind of like daydreaming kind of kind of stuff. I don't know. It's interesting. I uh
What have you been daydreaming about lately? Mr. Simon?
Well, I was daydreaming a lot today when I was like, you know, I was a little bit stoned and then it's like
But I kept like kind of nodding out a little bit. It was just so tired
It gives me this weed doesn't get me really tired. And so what was I daydreaming about?
Well, I mean it's like I kind of like work on my site and stuff like I used to like wake up like talking and thinking
I was still streaming because I stream so much
I would like wake up and do you is that like like how many times per month do you say you have that kind of experience?
I'm curious. I used to all the time when I was like when I was like streaming like for 12 hours like minimum
Like I like a lot of my old episodes last year like this one
I think it's like 12 hours probably like, you know, I went over probably 12 hours
That's when I fall asleep on the stream and yeah
But I used to wake up and then turn on the camera and then go all day
And then fall asleep try and either fall asleep with the stream on or try to turn it off or something like that
But I used to do that a lot now. I haven't done it in a long time. And so now I wake up normally
I don't but yeah, actually there was one time I fell asleep
And then someone was knocking on the door,
and I was talking my sleep telling him to come in
and come on the show and stuff like that.
And everyone was like, yeah, I don't remember it,
but it's like everyone was saying that was true.
So I am pretty deep sleeper sometimes though,
and I used to just really, really push it on streaming.
I was just so dedicated and did it every day.
But so addicted at one point now I now I get enough time and like you know
I'm trying to yesterday. I kind of took it to most of the day off and
Today I was like I'll just watch a rerun. You know this cuz it's like I kind of like I had fun the other night
I went to like this like money for 20s panel and like summer was up there
I think in a ghost and Alex McQueen at one point and this Harry Tazikus. I don't know if you heard him. He's like real
Kind of weird, but he's kind of funny and like we were just like bullshitting and laughing and it's been like so long since I
had like so much fun, like just like laughing and
That's good you had fun.
It was fun.
And I was like, I missed that.
And so I'm trying to get like, tell somewhere like,
come back and like, you know, hopefully like,
we can have some, like, and just like have more of that.
Well, you gotta figure out what those,
what the topics were that you were talking about
at that time that brought for fun.
I usually let them run wild.
Like I'm watching today and I said,
I didn't really say much.
I was kind of like, and I kind of have this weird look
on my face.
I kind of like, I can tell I'm kind of drunk.
But I would let people just go wild and stuff, I don't know, and talk about whatever we were talking about.
I wrote Nomad was on, and Joker was there, and I think Joker was botting my chat back
then.
I think I had like 263 people in the chat at one point that night, I was like, okay,
well that's a new record.
They went back down to like 50 or 60 or something.
You don't want to return to any, like I'm not saying you ever were, but you don't want
to go into like heavy drinking or anything?
No, I don't. Yeah. But you know, maybe sometimes things are in the past for a reason, right? I was drinking like I can drink like a bottle of vodka and a night sometimes, you know, I mix with orange juice and I would like wake up still drunk. And yeah, I would get just wasted.
I would drink a lot of voodoo Rangers, which I don't drink anymore because they're like pretty disgusting. But back then I was like loving them and walking in the taco truck and
I was kind of like a sloppy eater.
I mean, I was watching him, I was like, oh my God,
I look like I'm really savoring that food.
But yeah, I'm a little bit calmed down a little bit.
I'm a little bit more relaxed.
Good, you seem to be chill right now.
Last time I was like, I was saying,
I love you to everybody, you know, like everybody.
Like, I was like, I love that.
I love the chat.
Well, I feel like you just went through
a little bit of a gauntlet.
I feel like you brought it on yourself because you took on a situation that I don't think
you knew exactly what you were bargaining for, but no, I don't have any advice.
like, you know, and like talk about stuff and like, but then I don't like to be told what to do or who to have on, but I then again, it's like, I can get pulled into like, these vortexes of like, well, then it's like all this, like over, like, I'm like, I don't really turn anybody away, and it's like, so people, so people that come, you know, it's like, we focus on certain things, and it's like, maybe not exactly what I wanted for this show. And so, I got to consider that. And I'm trying to slow down right now. And
And I am finding new people in the chat all the time.
That's pretty cool.
Like, I mean, they used to get chased away or not.
They were made uncomfortable by a lot of the regulars and stuff.
And so it's nice to get to make meeting new people.
And I like that.
So I think it's growing back up again, you know, it's just like but uh, you know
I tried to say like I try to be the bigger person in this situation with Kate now
I was like I apologize because I did say terrible things and I mean
What is the situation with Kate and you as of current? I don't even know exactly what the status is
well
So she was going after me when I was in crystals chat and I was like why like was there like a underlying
Yeah, well, she was I was letting her on the show like she was like sit almost as a co-host for like a month or something like that
Yeah, I remember that and we were good and we were good up until and then I guess I took away her mod
And she's like I wasn't she's like I'm not mad about that
But then some people told me that she was mad about it, but I took away
Yeah, but oh one time Barry in her chat he modded me
And then she noticed that whole Kate and Barry connection is what has always kind of made me feel uncomfortable when it comes to
wanting to like, you know
Be in like Kate's chat or anything because he I don't know
I just it's something weird about them as I know they're not officially a couple whatever, but they kind of are
But it's like I think he like controls who her friends are and I just feel like
He would try to like attack me
And I don't want to be attacked.
I don't want any of that, but see, I don't know.
I'm confused about Kate.
She confuses me, because I really like her personality.
Like when I listened to her show and everything,
I really do, but I feel like she's like treacherous.
And I don't know why.
And I'm like, why are you treacherous, Kate?
Why and why do you keep...
very around. It's weird. I don't know. So that's why I called it goons and stuff like that before. But yeah, but I mean, do you know Q is like a co-host on Crystal and like he has control of yeah, he has control of the stream yard so he can come on and when he wants to control of it now. Oh, they're doing a little e b v s m I guess. Yeah.
Yeah, and he's born bomb or twice in a show like you know, well, he's dominating her and she wants to be dominated
Yeah, she's like a little sex kitten. I guess he's ruined
Oh, I got to make it a oh
Yeah, I'm gonna be more in there because that I love the one where it's like she was doing the Britney Spears. I
Want to
I just totally had like a
man I see this is the kind of thing that gets me in trouble I better not do that
well maybe I will I don't know I'll file it away but I just had like this I mean if I were to make
what I just visualized in the AI
I would, I would be able to get away with it strangely on the YouTube because it wouldn't
be against TOS, but it would fuck with their fucking minds to such an extent.
I mean, already I fucked with both their minds.
I mean, let's keep it real.
I don't want to take it too far because I feel like they're both very unstable people and I do not
want any attachment to any sort of you know weird actions that they may take in the near future
because you know sometimes you just have like a little bit of a sixth sense about that and I just
I was accused as of, I guess, today or yesterday of calling someone's dad or something.
I'm not calling anyone's parents, calling anyone's family.
I mean, like, who do you think I am?
Like the school counselor or something?
Like what the fuck?
No, I'm not calling your parents.
You know, just leave me alone. You're just mad and I don't have to name who I'm addressing because I'm sure that they're listening but
You know, just leave me alone. I made it known that I don't want anything to do with you. That's never going to change and
Yeah, you know if you have problems with your parents, that's your problem
Not mine. Yeah, and I'm going to blame some person on the internet who already said leave me alone
I did see on Samans today. They played this clip of it was like you just posted it again
It was I guess a few years ago. Maybe three or four years ago of clumsy
Threatening you and stuff and on on your live. I don't think I just did it again. I think
Sorry coming up in the algorithm for some reason
You know it's like cuz then Sam and at the same time he posted it and clumsy was laying in his bed in his boxers
With his arms behind his head like, you know
Flirting with Sam and I mean it was I or flirting or something he was a haystack
I might have missed that
Is he pulling down the blanket and stuff like that really? Yeah, he was pulling on the bike to review that
Whatever this clip is and I know what you're talking about
He said he might put it on rumble. He's like oh cuz Alex will like you know like uh like strike me
So I have to put this on rumble and I was just but um
And then it's like as clumsy then to play the clip where why am I going to strike you if it's been there all this time?
Yeah, you know, it's
Okay
woman
to
man
Why are so is there an increasing rate?
of your male peers becoming super dramatic as of late.
There is something going on.
I feel like I might have missed the meeting about this.
What is going on?
I don't know.
It's like, I mean, is that something to do with the moon
or something like, I don't know.
Guys already come in like,
kind of like some guys are getting,
getting, yeah, they're getting a little bit bitchy.
They're getting into the drama too much.
And, you know.
Yeah, this thing says they're homosexuals. Well, see I'm homosexual and I'm not like that
I don't think it has to do with sexuality, right?
I think it has to do with like I
Do think it has to do with like an like energy balance or imbalance even between
Women and masculine energy, but that's not necessarily tied into sexuality
Yeah, because Tommy James has always been pretty bitchy to me, and like talk about that
Don't do that. I'm sorry. Yeah, but
Okay, what do you want to talk about with that because obviously it's something that you wanted that's on your mind
So let's go. What do you want to talk about?
Well, like because they were saying like I guess I was even saying on that show I was watching today
Like he they taught me James had come on and like had like he was like
you know say oh you're on meth and I mean this is like last year he was saying that he's saying
all the same stuff that he's saying today. You're on meth? Yeah and he's like oh you're a drughead.
Oh well let me look let me tell you something um I think that he's actually your friendly neighborhood
discord drug dealer okay yeah I think that all this oh I'm gonna do all the drugs oh
I hope that law enforcement gets hip to it, or maybe another drug dealer is like,
aha, I'm going to take you down by reporting you.
I hope something happens to him because he is too cocky, and I'm tired of him endlessly
talking about me.
Yeah.
I hope that he just, you know.
Well someone in the chat said that like recently he was trying to sell his bicycle for like dope and then like he got beat up and the bike got stolen or something so
Maybe that was his story, but then he showed his foot and his foot was all like bloody and stuff and swollen
And he's like, oh, I got in a fight look what they did to my foot
I was like the what they stepped on your foot or something like that like that seems like a strange fight
It's I mean, maybe there was no fight
Also talking about him I understand this like he's like, you know, he's not my favorite
Terrible to me
He's the most disgusting human being well, I don't like that too. It's like there's all these
He is the most disgusting human being are you walking around with a weird infected foot?
I can't say I can't say I am like I mean I one time my foot was kind of like you know
Like you know, they get kind of like a split it split on the back
I just had to pay here and then it picks it all up, you know
But never had like that kind of leakage or whatever that shit is. I mean, it's like, you know
I don't even want to know what that is. I have not seen the footage or the stills and I yeah
Be looking at that. This wasn't pretty. It wasn't very pretty, you know. Yeah
Yeah
This was what's worse a streamer or the chatter? I don't know but I heard like someone say on this one on this one website
They said there's there's not much difference between
Watching Cyrax and being Cyrax or something or you know we're commenting on Cyrax. I'm being caught Cyra
We're just kind of interesting
It was a interesting look on like these low cows where it's like these people that like are so obsessed with low cows
And you know and thinking that are themselves probably low cows and it's probably some of the these
These like locale ranchers if you saw them in real life, you'd be like, oh my god
The most of them are just very anonymous and stuff chatters are watching the streamer complaining and
Complaining yeah, I know chatters do complain a lot
But then I can ignore the chat and then it's like then and then I like people that are like, you know
Streamers every guy respect because I'm a streamer. So I respect well
I sometimes I respect them but some of them are like lately. There's a big group of them that are like
Oh my gosh, Bita was just going off on me.
Every little thing and she's like,
well, what about Psyche?
What about Psyche?
What about...
For anything anybody said to her, she was like,
well, what?
It brings me up.
What was this?
This is yesterday on...
Oh.
I think it was on SamMans.
Yeah, it was on SamMans and she was complaining about summer.
She got into a fight with Summer about me
because Summer didn't hear about the Brandon stuff.
And then she was trying to explain.
Oh, and then it's like everything was like,
Anytime it needs anything anybody was doing it was always but look at what look what psyche did liquid psyche did and she's like so obsessed
And then she like she also said like anybody that comes to my show
She like tells not to come to my show and and so and I've seen her harass people that were on my show or even just in the chat
She harasses and they go to her show she harasses them and their chat and stuff and they're like
Oh, what'd you say about me over there blah blah blah blah, and then she has to go but they try to watch my
Staying to find them and stuff. We've even oh we have 300 glow here. Let me 300 glows a good guy
Oh wait, there is without a shirt again. Oh, he's wearing a shirt. I can't tell you know glow
I'm aware of
Yo, what's up?
What's up, he's he has no I was what I was when I was
But I guess didn't work out J-Dog wants to go out with me too J-Dog was like, oh will you go out with me?
Or I'll book you can go to a gay club at day. I he's like I'll dance with you at the gay club and stuff. Yeah. Oh
But he never we never did it. I didn't see him like how you girls doing tonight. What?
Oh my god, you got a big bottle of vodka
Yeah, three includes one of those people like I just keep forgiving because he's like, you know
Mexican
You know he's a nice wife. I like his wife and he has cats too. I like that about him. So it redeemed him from a
Guess he showed a gun. He's a porn bombs me before the sick hasn't come up
I think sick's afraid of the boycott. He's afraid of Kate. I think we're signal. Wait, is it still in effect?
Yeah, I mean it's like so I apologize and stuff and I said, you know what I said
I don't I don't even apologize for apology from her
I thought it was over
Oh, no, she's like still pushing that and you know, she's like, oh, this is an over psyche and she's like we're gonna
You know, we're taking him down. He's the he's the key. She's like he showed his true colors
He doesn't need to apologize. I've never accepted his apology blah blah blah and so I heard God's like the other night on her show
But she was like she's been like a lot of time just talking. It was like this guy KZ who we all thought was dead
because R.G. had told me he saw the obituary.
Yeah, he's supposed to be dead, right?
But now he's not dead?
He showed up in my chat on the panel.
He actually used a fake voice and then I was like,
is that KZ? And it was him.
And he was like, oh, he's alive.
He's alive. He's back from the dead.
He was in jail.
I don't know if he was contributed to his,
to his, that the rumor or whatever, but yeah.
He's back on the streets and you know, he was really happy the other night and yeah, I don't know
so the Kate was talking about that on her show and
Then they get into like there's there's so nosy like oh my gosh, you know
He should be kicked out of his apartment, but you know, they're all talking about
You know my family out of your apartment. Yeah, they're like, oh my gosh
He's probably a noise those those nice people like that live in the area so much
Like you know someone should tell a sister that he's on drugs and what he's doing online blah blah
And it's like they're just like so it's just like so nosy and
They're nosy. Yeah, really nosy. So that's what it is
They are there. I mean, it's like it's like really I think I don't go I don't go and say like things that are not my business
I'm not like saying, oh my gosh, what what maybe you should report on them if they're going to report on you
I mean, what are they doing?
Yeah, there's people usually in the chat that are like, you know just have this faceless people in the chat
It could be the same person on a sock puppet accounts or whatever. It's probably one person. Yeah, it's like
It says I think because someone says in the chat I think because people like Sandman are gay on the inside so having psyche around makes them uncomfortable because they are confronting their inner feelings with within me I know well I think I'm projected upon a lot I think there is like a lot of
Like Sandman is like seems to be like in love with like people like Barry sometimes and I don't know I don't know if he's like he has a crush on Zaya or something I don't know I think Sandman is by
I think he definitely has a crush on Zaya
Yeah
Yeah, because he gets very, like, funny and protective about it, and, like, I don't know, he's...
I mean, I haven't watched it, or...
Bromance.
Yeah.
But, um, you know, like, who else?
I mean, it's like, and...
I don't know, like, and Crystal, I'd say, I'd never had been on her panel,
because she'd always, like, said I was banned.
Yes, that's right.
She's got wives there.
Hola!
He's a really cute cat. He's a white cat. I love his white cat. He has a sign. He's cat and he's all
White yeah, it's all white. He's an all white cat. Do you have your white cat around?
Yeah, my white cat show. That's the
opposite of um, Lenore. I know.
I would be so cool to have a white cat. Have they seen each other? No.
Or is this his white cat? Well, sure. Lenore. Is it a boy or a girl, the white cat?
My white cat is a female, feline. Okay, short hair or long hair?
Oh, short hair. Oh, okay.
Yeah, he has I think he has three cats and like a lot of people have three or four cats. It's pretty well
She better be domestic. You don't want to have a feral cat if possible
Yeah
Well, I mean they're saying in case that I have a feral cat colony in my house. It's like, you know
Tux is like
He's still getting used to being there right probably because I did see him acting up a little bit on your right
And he was high on catnip that time where he swatted my hand and stuff
But now he's like now he comes into next it's next to me and he left me pet him
And he's like all used to me so he's not acting like fairly right
He was born here
I mean he was born like under the TV set and then yesterday he came in he comes right up to the Lola
Who's his mom and they smell each other?
I think they smell each other to make sure they're the right the right cat because it's something I don't know
But then and then
Well, can't they see they can they have problems. Yeah, they can see but it's like some of the cats look so alike though
I mean it is like so, you know, it's like
Yeah, like I'm cats are like around that look alike
Yeah, well, I mean a lot because I've seen some of the you know black cats like look alike and then it's I saw like a couple that look like tricks recently on like
The next door that I thought might have been really were they tricks? No because like one of them had the
The leg was a different color and then one of them I
Was the same one, but there's a lot that looked like him
Hmm. Yeah, there's a lot a lot of cats that look like him. I mean a couple came up at the same time
One time when I had a black cat that went missing,
I saw like this one sent me like,
oh, here's one over here.
And I was like, I just like was like really hoping it was her.
So I went and I was like, yeah, it's her.
I told the people and they're like, well,
this one was found this and it still couldn't have been her.
And I was like, oh, yeah, damn it.
But you know, it's like, I should have removed him.
But I think I wouldn't know tricks wouldn't know me.
I would recognize him if I did like see him.
Like, I mean, cause he's kind of like a distinct.
He has an attitude face.
Yeah, he does.
Yeah, he was like a little bit.
He has a little bit of an attitude face.
That's why I think that he's just
in like a different home right now.
I know it's like maybe wishful thinking,
but I've just, as soon as you told me what happened
and you know, when he didn't return,
I was just thinking, you know what?
I don't think he's gone.
I think that he's just like living a different life.
But he might not always stay there, who knows.
I don't think he's far from you.
I think he's, like, right down to the bookshelf.
No, they usually don't go very far.
I mean, they don't go far, like, but it's, like, then I would
think that he would, like, find his way back,
but maybe he walks a little bit.
But he would start to disappear, like, a little bit longer
and longer because he was, like, like.
But if, like, the other situation
is to where he's, like, a solo cat and doted on.
Yeah.
he might have picked that over you unfortunately because he was like having to compete for attention.
He would always fight with like you know email cats he would kind of like and then he was like nice
to Rudy but Rudy is like a little old man cat you know. Yeah Rudy's old he's not oh Rudy doesn't want to fight.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I mean, it's like oh, yeah Rudy is like Rudy's like
Where's he's found a corner table that he sits on now and he's like but he loves to like sleep on me and like and
He gets along with all the cats. Yeah, but yeah, but but tux actually the other night
He was here for the first time and overnight like because the next morning he met at the bedroom like walk
I was like, oh my god. He's here. And so he was like, you know
He wants to he wants to live there. Yeah, pork chop. You got pork chop. Yep. He's gonna bring pork chop up
Oh, that's a cute better to be the indoor cat. Haha. Yeah, I mean my cats are indoor outdoor
But it's like yeah, Rudy does say indoors sometimes he goes outside and stuff like that
He brought back a mouse once and but then they're like, oh my god, you know
Just like the act like I'm like the cats are just like, you know, they're only died is mice. Oh, we have sick here, too
I mean do you mind? It's there, you know behave. Hello
See, he hasn't been here in a while.
NAKER! NAKER! NAKER! NAKER! NAKER!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, okay, you're banned. I mean, what an idiot. I mean, it's like...
Well...
Ugh. Disgusting.
Well, by... I mean, that was what it's... I mean, what is their problem?
I mean, I don't understand people sometimes.
Oh God, other than that, that was a nice stream.
Yeah, I mean, it's like ridiculous.
Well, then I was trying to come back.
You know, you're banned for the rest of my life.
I don't want to talk to Steve.
Yeah, I know, he's banned.
I'm banning him right now.
He's banned.
I ban him from the stream.
What a jerk.
I mean, but yeah, I'm sorry.
I mean, it's like, I mean, people like you, like, you know,
encouraged him, but did you see Aldi?
What happened to Aldi on the bus recently?
Um a few things happened to him, but what happened recently? Well
He wouldn't let Saint use the bathroom and Saint was like I have to be let me in
And he's like and he was like inside the bathroom like dancing. He was wearing his African
dashiki or whatever it is
He was um wearing a wearing a cowboy hat. He has his foot is broken. Anyway
since I think Saint finally got in the bathroom and then
He turned off the street like I'm Aldi turned off Saint's stream
Which he had left on you know and so then I'm Aldi was just chilling in the bus
Like sitting in the chair like you know just hanging out on his stream and all of a sudden you just see this cup of piss
Hit him in the head the piss went in his mouth. Yeah, same had like filled up a whole bag of
Adam got and then he's like sitting there and he can't he has a broken foot so he can't get up and run and he goes
He goes, is that piss is that piss and he kept asking me
They might have gone kicked out after that cuz I saw him packing his bag and stuff like that
It was just been uncomfortable, but yeah, he was like that's what you get for messing with my stream and not letting me pee
I mean it was so gross and he went all in his mouth and stuff. Oh, I don't let's not be
Explicit about that. Thanks
Yeah, I you know, oh
What I love about
The internet and I guess what will in time be the future internal net is
That we have the power of creating whatever boundaries we want and in my world
There is nothing gross like that at all
Period
I made a new video
It's kind of like an 80s style like you like, but I feel like you I feel like you're like you've become the dark 80s
like in a way
Because you have the the uh, well, are you still gonna keep are you gonna keep streaming on the nightmare?
Yeah, this um, I have this this is I made this one. This is one of my favorite videos ever made actually
It's like an 80s has a glitch hop vapor wave style. So it's got the neon and stuff. Do you mind if I play real quick?
Yeah, play it. This is called the cult of the open eye and see if you
Okay, here we go
Neon static in the cathedral screen pixel ghost whisper what the smiles really mean
Everybody's talking everybody's selling dreams, but the truth leaks out between the broken seems
The Oracle buffering
I feel like doing a round-off backhand straight, but I wouldn't care if you're not the problem.
I like this.
I think it turned out pretty good. I don't know. I just had bias. I love my music, but um
I do want to tell you that the Claude released a new model called Mythos, but they changed
the name to Fable because Mythos had come out a few months ago and they're just letting
big companies, they're like, it's too powerful, it's too powerful, and actually yesterday
Yesterday the day before yesterday the government abandoned it for foreigners or something like that
And so they just took it away from everybody. They had a so I don't have you heard about that Alex. Are you still there?
You might have stepped away. Yeah, but that was it's crazy
So it's like because they don't want anybody using it right now. So
They did give everyone like, you know, they cleared their week their weeks
Whatever it's called like their quota the weekly quota
That was already out of it because the model does take up a lot of the
the
your your usage that you get and stuff, so I
Don't know. Oh, I don't know. I got hopefully didn't lose Alex, but
Yeah, I was thinking I might show like the saga we have the saga of
when I would got copyright struck and
Show you some of this.
Oh, yeah, I think I lost Alex.
But thank you, Alex.
I hope you come back soon.
Let's see, what do I got?
I'll try to put this on one second.
This is on Rumble.
I think this is a trip kick.
I never really watched this one, though, I don't think.
I was on Rumble, hold on.
Rumble, OK, here we go.
And then, after this, I might go to.
Sleep or something. I don't know. I'm already getting like a little bit. I take I take a hit of the weed and like, you know
Let's get kind of strong on me
So let's see what do we have on on this?
Yeah, I do want to talk to Alexandra about this guy blade and I guess like all these people are dying around him
That's pretty crazy. I also there's a really funny video. I remember watching of Alex, but I don't know if she won it played but
Let me see this though. Let me see
Let me see, there's Black Eyed Andy versus Stopped Speeding.
Okay, okay, let's see, what do I got?
I mean, this is when I started,
Chicken Cakes versus Tommy James, that looks entertaining.
Let me see, I guess I can watch any of these
because they're unremovable for a reason,
but let me see, I think I might have to go.
Nick went to, I see some of these people
I've never even seen.
Beat of, okay, let's see,
Q45 versus Mommy, Blogger, Reunion, Banter,
Too Spicy for YouTube, oh.
Tricia was just kicked out of a concert on censored version.
Okay, here, here we go.
I think this is it.
Carolous Kate, the end of Beedah's Kitties in Psyche.
Okay, Summer goes, fuck off on me,
Sam-Man versus Psyche.
Oh my God, that was funny.
Psyche versus Carolous Kate.
So we used to fight, yeah,
and first Janet on Beedah's Kitties.
Janet turns to pull up on Beedah on Psyche's panel.
That was not funny.
Yeah, but here's some of the battle to the answer the mystery I guess we can watch this together
This is when I got like struck by the Tony like five times in a day or whatever or like 11 times of the day actually
So check it out. Let's watch a little bit of that. I can see what goes on here. Electra's here
Here I am. I was in such a bad mood when this happened
I'm worried about you right now
I'm fine
I'm gonna link it back up guys. I know I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine
You're not
That shower that water and your pores and everything it'll it'll give you a bit of little life in you
You need a little life to do
I won't do it. You can't be that fast no one with this shit. I can tell you my channel back
I'm not gonna do it. I'm not gonna do that baby to get your channel back. You got to be better than what you're doing right now
Hey
Look DJ
We're gonna save your channel psyche. We're saving your channel. Hi ladies
Well, if this chick would stop talking for a sec. Sorry. No disrespect, but I'm going to try to talk
So we're gonna fix your channel psyche. It's okay. I don't mean to be disrespectful. Sorry. That was rude
But I'm just out here. This is the song that I made and it's been taken. It's been taken over by some idiot
So psyche
I want to share on the screen this is what we're doing we're going to share right now
where I made the song so it will be very obvious that I made it and it's published on that channel
on Udio under my name and I gave psyche permission to use it as many times as he wants I made him
You realize YouTube isn't they they're not gonna what did you say go to this extent to listen to this stuff though, right?
Like we know that you made it, but oh, no
I know people that work for Google that work for YouTube that work for Google that I'm contacting with this video and
Time stamps so that they're
They're going to watch it. Oh
I'm sure they are I
I'm sure
you realize they don't care about pee pee on channels like this you're laughing
did I laugh did you hear a giggle why are you laughing where's the laughing
where's the laughing yeah I heard you laughing when did anyone else hear me
laughing I don't think I snickered
Is there anything else you want for me to psych you out?
I came up because you asked me to,
but it looks like your army of hug boxes here, so.
Fuck I didn't even see anything. I've been like nothing but cordial. I'm like up here. Just take the
One more thing to ask for you. Okay, everyone think that's for you. I want you to apologize to be the
She doesn't have to do that
Like listen bitch, I don't subscribe to you. Keep trying and being obsessed about me every day. I don't really care
whole song
And it's published on this site.
So published by me, not by that other guy.
And this is where it was created.
So that guy cannot have a copyright on it.
I'm also going to the government site
where he got the copyright on it.
And I'm going to have that legally removed.
Thank you.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Alexa.
Of course, I mean
Can I say something good and I reach out to you yesterday? I was like, please please please please like like he needs this
Like people think I'm not trying to like help him out as much as I can
He's not listening like not to me. No summer not Christine
We've been trying to like tell him it's gonna be okay like one step at a time and
Like psyche come on do it just kind of why we need you to get it together. Yeah, you
Everybody else is fighting for you. You have to pull it together. We got to get you in the shower
We got to get your mojo back up, dude. You guys there are two people he will listen to one is DJ
Electra, okay
DJ Electra, I'm gonna share with you he has been
He's being intimidated by these group of people.
He is allowing them to take over his channel.
He's giving them access to his panel.
He's giving them wrenches.
He's doing all kinds of bullshit
to try to get them to stop doing what they're doing.
He doesn't understand this is not the way to do it.
That when Monday comes, it will be a different ballpark.
And what a few of us other ones are going to do come Monday. He needs to stop outing over this right now
Um, definitely giving them wrenches is is not the best way to go about it because then they have access
They can block people they can hide people from your channel and that's just not the way to go
And the best thing to do, honestly, is ignore them as much as you can.
They get bored when you ignore them, and then they stop trying to harass you.
However, this person that has gone to the length of copyrighting a song, which costs like 50 bucks to do, by the way.
So this guy is out 50 bucks, and he went, he lied to the government.
We could sue his ass.
He lied to the copyright claim of the government.
That's ridiculous.
So I'm not gonna get him struck, Doug D.
I only played it for like 30 seconds
and I'm showing him that I own that song.
I made it.
So anyways, too many trolls.
They are exhausting, Psyche.
I get it.
They are exhausting, but you're stronger than that.
There's one guy can like just be copyright strike me like you know you made this song
We have proof. She made the song for me. It was a gift to me
I put this on you know now and now it's like no Q is playing it has an intro song Vita
No, it's on Q's channel. He gave it to Q. So psyche
This is what I want to say why why DJ is doing all this amazing stuff to help you keep this channel
Can we please get you in the shower get some life back in you? You have to be strong to get through this
You summer you want me to get naked and a camera and get in the shower now, baby in this hour
I don't want to get naked. I don't need you get this channel struck. No, I'm not
I'm taking a shower. I don't see a shower clothes. I'll think it naked. I'll be in the shower
There's a minute have the blur the blur
We don't need you to form on your own channel
Yeah, no, we're trying to keep this one good and get your other one to be okay
Are you ever strike on this channel because of the same on the same thing strike in the songs
He also put out. He also gave it to Q to use on his channel
And whenever he wants to he said he said he bought the copyright to it
YouTube is like they rejected the first claim I've made another claim I talked to the yeah
But he bought a false copyright because he didn't make the song
Yeah, perfect. What happened is this what happened is this guy took the song from YouTube
He just recorded it or downloaded it and he sent it to the copyright board, which is a government agency
That's how you get a copyright on a song. I didn't think I needed to copyright my songs
I didn't realize I had to pay $50 for something that I'm doing free to
Help my friends to make intros for their channels. I didn't realize trolls. We're gonna take it this far
It's it's just it's actually sad that that's his life that he feels like he needs to
go and
Take steal someone else's music that they made from AI. So it's not even I didn't write the actual song
I wrote the lyrics but
This common mistake doubles your electricity bill and big energy is trying to hide this fix
But just the fact that he's taking this and taking it so far. It's just ridiculous and whatever Tony whatever his name is
Yeah, but he but he apparently copyrighted it sounded so real
Copyright board it so it takes like a month and a half for them to finalize it
So they're probably reviewing it right now, but they give you a certificate
While they're reviewing it that says that you temporarily have copyright for this song
So it's probably not finalized yet. That's why it's not showing up
Universally on YouTube. This is not showing up on my channel. It's not showing up on
Any of my songs where I played it? So it's not universal on YouTube yet
So he he doesn't even have it finalized yet
So I'm contacting the copyright board as well. So
No, so he knows Tony. It's Tony. It's Tony. Who is it that owns it Tony or this Brian? I
Can't believe that he has this much time on his hands to concentrate on something like this. No, but yeah
That's not I don't even know if that's who he is. I don't even know who this guy is you guys
I'm just I just read a name. I just read the name that says on my on my YouTube
Just I'm gonna and he says it's him. I'm just reading the name off that what it says
Yeah, the person that's suing me legally and I'm in a legal situation with this person
I'll read the name on the on the lawsuit. Okay? Yeah
Exactly
Okay, he's saying it's weird. Yeah, he's saying you're weird. Okay, so Kate. Well, okay, you're not weird
Yeah, well take away her wrench and block her from your channel
Why do you allow these trolls to be on your chat? They're driving you insane psyche?
We've been trying to handle them by timing them out and hiding them, but then he turns around and gives them wrenches
Take away her wrench
She's a troll
No, Kate
Kate I'll I'll let you keep your wrench if you know
Si if you if you take up the take up the strikes if you take up the straight cuz she's behind them
Take up the strikes. I'll give you a wrench. Okay, I'm bargaining. It will never work
He will lose his channel because of the way he's bargaining and not listening to what you or I are even saying
Okay, yeah, it's useless to even be up here. I'm gonna go ahead and do something about this instead of being
Allowing these trolls to run your channel. I'm actually gonna go make a video
Send it to YouTube put it on Twitter tag YouTube
Make sure they see it get it to the right people
And if you're not gonna take the time to contact YouTube and do this yourself. I can't help you
I can't go to your channel unless you make me a manager on your channel. I will I will make you man
I'll make you manager right now. Okay. I'm hearing no address
I don't know as soon as I can figure out I have to figure out how to add a manager
But I will I just manage her on stream yard as well. Okay. She doesn't want to deal with trolls you have in the chat
I know I'm gonna do either ignore the chat guys
I had the worst role in the chat calls me pdf the chat
But you're giving me we can handle that if you wouldn't give him wrenches
Yeah, I won't in black RG. No Kate has a wrench RG has a wrench or PG. Whatever his name is has a wrench. Hold on
Hold on. Let's see Kate black RG
Hold on
Right now those two
Are the ones
Kate you are saying nasty shit get out of here
You know just have you know, you're the one that's supposed to be in charge
You're the pilot and then you have people up here that are helping you out keep it together
But you're just I don't know I can't say much but listen to us at all
You're worried about, you know, if you go into Kate's chat right now and you write any nasty thing about her or any of her audience
You get permanently they get done. They're out. You can't even take her link
But then you're like letting DJ Electro who's trying to help you out like clear this shit get this respected over and over
I don't really give a shit. I try my best, you know
Well, no, I wasn't trying to be that I'm like
It's just like have a backbone and do something do what you think is right like do what you think
people. It's crazy to me. I'm
not scared of people. I was
you were supposed to be in
control. Am I wrong? Am I like
going crazy here? Kate, are you
disrespecting me? You're
disrespecting me. Kate says
disrespect me in the chat.
Look at look at the acceptance
that you need from like
anybody, whether it's me or
anybody in the chat. Like
focus on what you need to do
I'm trying to you
for your channel.
You want us around and stuff and we're trying to give you advice on things and I mean
You know, I mean look at you like you need to go take a shower
You need to take a break from this for a couple hours and get you together. You are fucking crashing out right here on screen
It's not cool dude. Let's go get
How are you?
Will you stop Christine you know, I won't stop
You haven't helped once if anything you really I haven't helped I have
You done letting chicken shit in your house psych do be just right listen to her you sell some rest
Log off. You're not good to anybody and you're not good to your channel if you're not thinking clearly
And you're not a hundred percent. Okay, the other thing is you
Well, no beat is right though. You need to take care of yourself. Yeah, you have to dude. You have to
Guys, the channel was last
Thank you. Thank you. Listen, dude. Listen. Thank you. Thank you. Just give me two minutes. Give me two minutes, baby
It's summer if you just logged off for a little bit when took your shower got you grounded again
And then you could come back, but this is not helping the situation at all okay. It's okay. I'll crash them
I'll crash them burn. You know
You're causing so many more situations for yourself. Now you're playing victim now. You're actually playing
So much about wrenches and so less about your health and your mental state right now
Oh, you care about his wrenches. You're an old hag and I don't know. That's
And you're a liar you're a liar liar and you guys were so confident last night that he wouldn't lose his channel
What happens? He loses his channel
That's fix we have
Because it's not your channel
It's too bad
Let the man get some rest. Think clearly and let him make his own decisions.
Okay, that's enough.
Oh, you have the mean streets, huh?
Mean streets of YouTube.
Well, everything turned out okay, basically.
I mean, it's like, not like I could turn it out worse.
That was funny.
Okay, I'll just, I'm gonna probably like, take a nap or something.
We'd hit me.
So but hold on. Thank you for coming though guys. Even the lurkers, you know
Thanks for the video. Thanks for the screen screen time
We'll wait back the way back machine
Here I'll play this on the way out since it was a classic
enjoy
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that
trash then she flips rage queen mad at me girl please the show runs on caffeine
sides twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we
cut the feed no shame but the chats on fire can't tame this flame this ain't
your mama's podcast this a runaway train welcome to the madness buckle up
tight boob flashing on cam chat losing their minds Michael getting gong Alex
taking flight it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night
Haze got him simpin' hearts in the chat
But she ain't got time for a dude like that
Diamond flirtin' hard, let the girls react
It's a freak show party, no filter, all facts
Yo, facts
Yo, yo, Michael drops a line, gong, not tonight
Alex tried to joke, boom, sent into the night
Panel lookin' sideways, someone's gotta fight
Producers on mute, prayin' this don't spike
Diamonds feelin' spicy, shirts slippin' down low
Oops, she says we're the wink, that's the whole show
Sighs half asleep but still cracking jokes
Slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules, just roles we pretend to play
One hand on the mute, other letting it spray
It's a circus, a riot, a beautiful mess
One wrong word and we're trending in the press
Welcome to the madness, buckle up
tight boob splashing on cam chat losing their minds michael getting gong to alex taking flight
it's wild it's wrong and we do it every night page got him simping hearts in the chat but she
ain't got time for a dude like that diamond flirting hard let the grip it's a freak show party no
filter all facts yeah lights out one more round and beat is on the line we crash at the same time
Enjoy the ride, welcome to the mad, welcome to the madness